Okay, welcome back, everyone.
好的，欢迎大家回来。
Our next session is on security and Mac.
我们下一场讨论的主题是安全性和Mac电脑。
Greg Partridge is Professor and Chair of the computer science department at
格雷格·帕特里奇是科罗拉多州立大学计算机科学系的教授兼系主任，他将主持这次会议。
Colorado State University and would be chairing this session.
科罗拉多州立大学将主持这次会议。
So I'll hand it off to you Craig, go ahead please.
那么我就交给你了，克雷格，请开始吧。
>> All right, thank you.
好的，谢谢。
And I'm gonna immediately hand it over to the next person so
我将立即把它交给下一个人，所以
we'll go straight to the first talk for the session.
我们将直接进入本环节的第一个报告。
>> Zhiyi Zhang is a fifth year PhD student at the Internet research lab at UCLA.
>> 致毅张是加州大学洛杉矶分校互联网研究实验室的一名五年级博士研究生。
His main research interests are in networking, and in network security.
他的主要研究兴趣在于网络技术以及网络安全。
And he will be talking about rolling out NDN for DDoS mitigation.
他将会讨论部署NDN来缓解DDoS攻击。
>> Okay, perfect.
>> 好的，完美。
We'll get started.
我们将开始。
Yeah, so I'm glad to be here.
是的，所以我很高兴能来到这里。
I'm Zhiyi from UCLA.
我是来自加州大学洛杉矶分校的智毅。
And, this work is called rolling out NDN for DDoS mitigation,
这项工作被称为部署NDN以缓解DDoS攻击，
and this is also done by a Sichen from UCLA, Angelos from Virginia Tech,
这项工作也是由来自加州大学洛杉矶分校的Sichen和来自弗吉尼亚理工学院的Angelos完成的，
Eric from George Mason, and Alicia from UCLA.
埃里克来自乔治梅森大学，而艾丽西亚来自加州大学洛杉矶分校。
So, okay.
所以，好的。
So, DDoS, I mentioned it here, it can be a killer app.
所以，DDoS，我在这里提到它，它可以成为一款杀手级应用程序。
So, we all know that DDoS has plagued the internet for decades.
所以，我们都知道DDoS已经困扰互联网几十年了。
And, as we all know, the DDoS is by large
所以，我们都知道DDoS已经在很大程度上
enabled by some TCPIPs on, properties.
影响了一些基于TCP/IP的网络属性。
So therefore the DDoS can be a killer app,
因此，分布式拒绝服务攻击可以成为一种致命应用程序，
to push some architectural changes of today's internet.
推动当今互联网架构的一些变革。
And your at any income so
~!@#$%^&*()
our candidate NDN has intrinsic DDoS mitigation properties.
我们的候选者NDN具有内在的DDoS缓解特性。
This includes, for example, off by design, we have state of affording,
这包括了例如从设计上就排除了某些功能，我们拥有承受的状态，
we have named to provide better traffic insights.
我们已命名以提供更好的流量洞察。
And we can eliminate the reflection attack because the data
我们可以消除反射攻击，因为数据
must follow the same path of interest.
必须沿着兴趣的相同路径。
And before talking about how to bring the NDN to reality, to mitigate DDoS attacks,
在讨论如何将NDN变为现实以缓解DDoS攻击之前，
let's first see how today's industry practice to mitigate DDoS.
让我们首先看看当今行业如何实践以缓解DDoS攻击。
So first, I show this picture of a CDN network.
首先，我展示了这张CDN网络的图片。
So we have lines that are in their own networks.
所以我们有的线路是在它们自己的网络中。
They connect to the CDN nodes where which also add edge, and
它们连接到CDN节点，这些节点还增加了边缘计算功能，
those CDN nodes connects to the servers as Roger and think finally reach the server.
这些CDN节点连接到服务器，如同Roger所想的，最终到达了服务器。
So this is how normally CDN is like, but
这就是CDN平时的样子，但是
things will be different when there's a DDoS.
这就是CDN平时的样子，但是当发生DDoS攻击时，情况就会有所不同。
So CDN providers, they have already started providing DDoS mitigation
所以CDN提供商们已经开始提供DDoS缓解服务，利用他们现有的CDN基础设施。
And when DDoS happened, as you can see here.
当DDoS攻击发生时，正如你在这里看到的。
Instead of directly steering the traffic to the Azure altar of the server,
而不是直接将流量引导到服务器的Azure祭坛上，
the steering the traffic to the MaaS,
而将流量引导至MaaS（Mitigation as a Service），
which is mitigation as a service infrastructure for DDoS mitigation.
该服务是用于DDoS缓解的缓解即服务（Mitigation as a Service）基础设施。
So in this MaaS they do, for example, TLS decryption,
所以在这个缓解即服务（MaaS）中，他们会进行例如TLS解密，
they do deep packet inspection, the job those suspect packets.
所以在这个缓解即服务（MaaS）中，他们会进行例如TLS解密，他们进行深度包检查，处理那些可疑的数据包。And then after this so-called traffic scrambling,
And then after this so called traffic scrambling,
然后在所谓的流量混淆之后，
they steer the plane traffic to the edge router of the server and
他们将飞机的流量引导到服务器的边缘路由器，然后在所谓的流量混淆之后，最终到达服务器。
finally reached the server.
最终到达服务器。
But the thing is how good is today's DDoS mitigation so.
但问题是，今天的DDoS缓解措施有多有效。
First a works, definitely works, and
首先一个作品，绝对有效，而且
there has been several successful mitigated the DDoS events.
已成功缓解了多起DDoS事件。
However, there are several issues first, deep packet inspection DPI
然而，首先存在几个问题，深度包检查DPI
with TLS traffic is hard, because we all know that today's TLS and
由于我们都知道，今天的TLS流量很难处理，因为
HTTPS has dominated the web application of internet.
HTTPS已经成为互联网Web应用的主宰。
And to do DPI, this usually requires extra infrastructure like MaaS.
为了进行深度包检测(DPI)，这通常需要额外的基础设施，比如像MaaS（金属即服务）这样的系统。
And also, the the mitigation approach used by today's practice
而且，当今实践中使用的缓解方法
is purely to blackhole or backhaul, the attack traffic.
是为了将攻击流量进行黑洞处理或回传。
But this will this surely cause large collateral damages to those
但这肯定会对那些
good clients which is to deny the service of good clients.
这无疑会拒绝优质客户的服务。
And also, the problem is a slow reaction.
同时，问题还在于反应迟缓。
And in this work we want to propose our FITT over NDM for DDoS mitigation.
在这项工作中，我们想提出将我们的FITT应用于NDM之上，以缓解DDoS攻击。
So FITT is set for 10 grand internet interest traffic throttling FITT in short,
因此，FITT被设定为10G大规模互联网流量限制，简称FITT。
and this is a DDoS based DDoS mitigation system, utilizing ADN stateful forwarding.
这是一个基于DDoS的DDoS缓解系统，利用ADN有状态转发。
And for the sake of time, I won't cover the details of how FITT is working.
为了节省时间，我不会详细介绍FITT的工作原理。
I put the link of our technical report here, so
我在这里放了我们技术报告的链接，所以
people can interested can check this tr.
I have placed the link to our technical report here, so people who are interested can check this translation. And in this talk I want to focus on the incremental deployment of NDN and...
And in this talk I want to focus on the incremental deployment of NDN and
在这次演讲中，我想重点讨论NDN的渐进式部署以及...
FITT, using today's CDN boxes.
FITT, 利用当今的CDN盒子。
And importantly we want to analyse the incentives here.
而且重要的是，我们想要分析这里的激励因素。
And this incremental deployment approach also works for other and NDS,
这种增量部署方法也适用于其他NDS。
ICN DDoS mitigation mechanisms as well.
ICN分布式拒绝服务攻击缓解机制同样适用。
And through this talk, I want to show that first NDN and FITT,
通过这次讲话，我想展示首先NDN和FITT，
they help CDN to the better.
它们帮助CDN更好地发挥作用。
To be more specific,
为了更具体说明，
it provides both CDN DDoS mitigation services with even smaller budget.
它提供了即便预算更小的CDN DDoS缓解服务。
So let's see how it works.
那么让我们来看看它是如何工作的。
So first we want to deploy our NDN and FITT at edges.
首先，我们想要在边缘部署我们的NDN和FITT。
When I say at edges, is we deploy
在边缘部署指的是我们部署
NDN plus FITT on all the CDN boxes.
NDN加上FITT在所有的CDN设备上。
As shown here, and we also deploy NDN at the edge router of the server and
在这里所示，我们还在服务器的边缘路由器上部署了NDN。
we also like the server to be NDN and FITT aware.
我们还希望服务器具有NDN和FITT的感知能力。
And between the CDN and those and edge servers, and
并且在CDN与那些边缘服务器之间，还有
servers as realtors we build NDN tunnels.
服务器作为中介，我们构建了NDN隧道。
And when DDoS happens, first of end of the server to react first,
当DDoS攻击发生时，首先是服务器首当其冲地做出反应。
because the server is the one who suffered from the DDoS.
因为服务器是遭受DDoS攻击的对象。
So it shows that, it's an instant feedback to the systems in that I got the DDoS
所以这表明，这是对系统的即时反馈，即我遭受了DDoS攻击。
attack, and the prefix that is under attack is slash a slash me slash C.
攻击的目标是斜杠a斜杠me斜杠C前缀。
And if the server knows which of those interests packets are malicious,
如果服务器知道哪些兴趣包是恶意的，
they can also explicitly put those interest names into that our facts or
它们还可以将这些恶意的兴趣名称显式地放入我们的事实中，或者至少放入一个布隆过滤器中。
into at least into a bloom filter.
至少放入一个布隆过滤器中。
And, in the message the server have also specify what's the request
在消息中，服务器还指定了请求的内容。
per second capacity of the server, under this prefix.
服务器在该前缀下的每秒处理能力。
And after that, the feedback will arrive at the server azure router,
之后，反馈将会到达服务器Azure路由器，
the sever azure router will first check
服务器Azure路由器首先将会检查
the pen interest table ,to see those matched flows or packets.
查看那些匹配的流量或数据包的兴趣表。
And then create a new feedback to downstreams to those downstreams
然后向下游创建一个新的反馈。
where the suspect traffic is from, and then through the NDN tunnels
来自哪里的可疑流量，然后通过NDN隧道
those feedback will finally reach the CDN boxes hop by hop.
这些反馈将逐跳最终到达CDN设备。
And when the CDN knows reached get the get feedback, it can start throttling
当CDN设备知道已经获得了反馈后，它可以开始进行流量限制。
traffic from suspect inspects and only under the prefix slash a slash b slash c.
来自怀疑检查的流量，仅在前缀/a/b/c/下。
And either and even more further deployments of our NDA FITT,
以及我们的NDA FITT的进一步部署，甚至更多。
we can also have the clients night works to have as router for NDN.
我们还可以让客户的夜间工作充当NDN的路由器。
For example, a smart home we can have a smart home with a NDN azure router.
例如，我们可以拥有一个带有NDN azure路由器的智能家居。
And in this case, we can further push the traffic throttling into edges.
在这种情况下，我们可以进一步将流量限制推至网络边缘。
And in this case, you can even do some reinforcement throttling,
在这种情况下，你甚至可以进行一些加强的流量限制，
which means, we can reinforce the throttling for
这意味着，我们可以对那些恶意客户端进行加强的流量限制，并为那些温顺的客户端解除限制。
those rogue clients and release the throttling for those tame clients.
对那些恶意客户端加强流量限制，并为那些温顺的客户端解除限制。
And as I mentioned, I want to analyze the incentives of this NDN and
并且正如我提到的，我想分析这个NDN的激励机制。
FITT deployment.
FITT部署。
The first FITT and NDN to both CDN DDoS mitigation because NDN
FITT和NDN首次共同对CDN进行DDoS攻击缓解，因为NDN
provides good cache and and network storage, and
提供良好的缓存和网络存储，以及
FITT provides DDoS mitigation properties and functionalities.
FITT提供DDoS缓解属性和功能。
And then there's no need as I shown before, there's no need for
然后就像我之前展示的，没有必要
additional hardware or MaaS infrastructure to do decentralized packet,
进行去中心化数据包的额外硬件或MaaS基础设施，
deep packet inspection or scrubbing.
深度数据包检查或清洗。
And we see nicely that FITT and the NDN use a smaller
我们可以清楚地看到，FITT和NDN使用了更小的
resource footprint compared with today's practice,
我们可以清楚地看到，FITT和NDN使用了更小的资源占用与现今的做法相比，这是TLS终止加上DPI加上流量混淆。
which is TLS termination plus DPI plus traffic scrambling.
它是TLS终止加上DPI加上流量混淆。
And I proved my statement by this a real world deployment evaluation,
我通过这个真实世界部署评估来证明我的观点，
on the one side we deploy FITT over NDN of course, and over the IP.
在一方面，我们当然是在NDN（命名数据网络）上部署FITT，同时也在IP上部署。
And then on the other side we use Squid which is a popular CDN software stack.
在另一方面，我们使用Squid，这是一个流行的CDN（内容分发网络）软件栈。
We use the Squid for CDN and TLS termination.
我们使用Squid进行CDN和TLS终止。
We didn't even add the scrubbing and the TLS forwarding logic in the Squid side.
我们甚至没有在Squid端添加清洗和TLS转发逻辑。
And then we compare the overhead of these two and
然后我们比较了这两者的开销。
we found that FITT plus NDN only requires like one-fifth CPU memory and
我们发现，FITT 加上 NDN 只需要大约五分之一的 CPU 内存和
one-thirds of the bandwidth under the same load.
相同负载下，仅需三分之一的带宽。
And then I want to talk about the advantages of FITT in DDoS mitigation.
然后我想谈谈FITT在DDoS缓解中的优势。
So compared with today's centralized mitigation, or
所以与当今的集中式缓解相比，或者
using black hole or backhaul, FITT, it does distributed throttling and
使用黑洞或回程，FITT实现了分布式限流，
then we have Fine granularity because we do per prefix at real attack origin.
然后我们拥有了细粒度控制，因为我们在真实攻击源处按前缀进行操作。
So this will minimize the collateral damage to benign traffic.
因此，这将最大程度地减少对良性流量的附带损害。
And we can do Fast reaction because we only
因此，我们可以做出快速反应，因为我们仅需
require one-way delay from the server to edge to start throttling.
因此，我们可以做出快速反应，因为我们仅需从服务器到边缘的单向延迟来开始节流。And we see that FITT is enabled by NDN's architectural properties.
And we see that FITT is enabled by NDN's architectural properties.
我们看到，FITT得以实现是由于NDN的架构特性。
Which is first names provides us good insights of the traffic,
该名字为我们提供了对流量的良好洞察，
compare based IP plus port.
基于IP加端口进行比较。
Therefore, we can do fine-grained traffic classification and throttling.
因此，我们可以进行细粒度的流量分类和限速。
The second is to have Stateful forwarding.
第二是要有状态的转发。
And this allows FITT to track those real attack or ranges.
这使得FITT能够追踪那些真实的攻击或范围。
And then the takeaways of this talk, we wanna say is that first, the architecture
然后，这次演讲的要点，我们想说的是，首先，架构
actually plays an important role in DDoS resilience and mitigation.
实际上在DDoS的韧性和缓解方面扮演了重要的角色。
This appears at the NDN versus today's TCP IP.
这出现在NDN与当今的TCP/IP之间的比较中。
And obviously that DDoS have a killer app to push the deployment potentially.
显然，分布式拒绝服务攻击可能成为一种推动部署的杀手级应用程序。
And through our work we show that FITT and NDN can be incrementally
通过我们的工作，我们展示了FITT和NDN可以逐步
deployed over to this city in boxes without any further burden or
通过我们的工作，我们展示了FITT和NDN可以逐步部署到这个城市的箱子中，而无需任何额外的负担或overhead, without any further hardware and MEMS infrastructure.
overhead, without any further hardware and MEMS infrastructure.
额外的开销，无需任何进一步的硬件和MEMS基础设施。
So there is motivation here to deploy FITT and NDN in today's CDN boxes.
因此，有动机在当今的CDN盒子中部署FITT和NDN。
And that's all for my talk, thank you, gracias.
这就是我演讲的全部内容，谢谢，感谢。
>> Thank you, so we have a question.
谢谢，所以我们有一个问题。
How does FITT detect the attackers use valid name prefixes and
FITT 如何检测攻击者使用有效的名称前缀和
invalid name suffixes?
FITT 如何检测攻击者使用有效的名称前缀和无效的名称后缀？
>> Yeah, so for example,
>> 是的，例如，
those valid prefix plus invalid suffix to reach the server.
这些有效的前缀加上无效的后缀以到达服务器。
The server will know that there's no corresponding data or
服务器会知道没有对应的数据或
service that can be replied to the none existing,
服务器可以回应不存在的服务，
actually this to reply to this attack traffic.
实际上是为了回应这种攻击流量。
So therefore, the server can be aware of this interest back is their email id.
因此，服务器可以知道回传的兴趣是它们的电子邮件ID。
So when they send back the FITT, the feedback to the network,
因此，当他们发送回FITT，即对网络的反馈时，
they can explicitly put those names into the Bloom filter.
他们可以将这些名称明确地放入布隆过滤器中。
So that later the edge and the CDN boxes, they can check their pending
因此，之后边缘节点和CDN设备就可以检查它们的待处理内容。
interest table and find where those packets are sent from.
因此，可以追溯到真正的攻击者，并找到这些数据包的发送来源。
And in this way, we can trace back to the real attackers and
find the source from which these packets were sent. And then, 对该接口的该前缀执行流量限制。
do traffic throttling to that prefix to that interface.
对该接口的该前缀执行流量限制。
To mitigate the DDoS attack.
为了缓解DDoS攻击。
>> Cool, thank you.
>> 酷，谢谢你。
I think what we just have is a sassy remark from Dave Moran,
我认为我们刚刚听到的是Dave Moran的一句嘲讽的话。
which would be characteristic.
这是他的典型特征。
He likes to talk and
他喜欢说话并且……
then makes the comment that if it works too well maybe people won't deploy NDN.
然后他评论说，如果它工作得太好，也许人们就不会部署NDN了。
I wanted to ask a related question.
~!@#$%^&*()
So this is one particular style of DDoS attack which is, you are attacking with
所以这是一种特定类型的DDoS攻击，即你正在发起攻击
interests to create an overwhelming volume of interests and or traffic.
兴趣洪水攻击，以产生压倒性的兴趣请求量或流量。
But the other form of DDoS attack that NDN is vulnerable to is ones that cause
但NDN容易受到的另一种DDoS攻击形式是那些造成
cache thrashing in the intermediate nodes,
缓存抖动问题，这主要发生在中间节点上，
where you request vast amounts of valid data that you don't actually care about.
你请求大量你实际上并不关心的有效数据。
[COUGH] But you do this to drive the actual valuable content out of the caches,
但你这么做是为了将真正有价值的内容从缓存中驱逐出去，
and so you end up causing popular content to be requested correctly over and
而你最终导致热门内容被正确地一次又一次地从源头请求。
over from the source.
从源头传送过来。
Does FITT help at all with that?
FITT有助于这方面吗？
>> For now?
>> 目前来说？
No, because the current implementation of FITT only protects the applications.
不，因为目前的FITT实现只保护了应用程序。
But I think what you mentioned, the DDoS attack scenario,
但我认为你提到的那种DDoS攻击场景，
it actually won't really over bloom the server.
实际上它并不会真的使服务器过载。
And if the attacker is smart enough to find enough number of content to
如果攻击者足够聪明，找到足够多的内容来
keep replacing the content store, which means there will be a large
持续替换内容存储，这意味着将会有大量
number of valid entries reaching at the server to overwhelm the server.
大量有效的请求达到服务器，以至于服务器不堪重负。
In this case, FITT can help because,
在这种情况下，FITT可以提供帮助，因为，
in this case the server can tell the FITT network seen that okay,
在这种情况下，服务器可以告诉FITT网络看到了，好的，
this perfect slash A, slash B or some other prefix are under attack.
这个完美的斜线A、斜线B或者其他前缀正在遭受攻击。
And I would expect RPS requests per second, even for
我预计即使是每秒请求量（RPS），也会有
example, the content delivery service.
例子，内容分发服务。
And with this RPS, even with these RPS,
即便有这些RPS，
those edge servers as routers like the CDN boxes,
这些边缘服务器就像CDN设备一样充当路由器，
they both wrote the traffic to meet the RPS requirement specified by the server.
它们都记录了流量以满足服务器指定的每秒请求量(RPS)要求。
So yes, in this says, yes,
所以是的，在这里它说，是的，
it can stop those valid packets overwhelming.
它可以阻止那些有效数据包的过载。
>> Cool, okay, well, we've now hit our time limit.
好的，我们现在已经到了时间限制。
So thank you very much for an interesting talk.
非常感谢您精彩的演讲。
Obviously, I see there's some discussion going on in the chat group and
显然，我看到聊天群里正在进行一些讨论，
you may wish to join it and talk with them more about your work.
你可能会想加入他们，并且更多地和他们讨论你的工作。
Yes, sure.
好的，当然可以。
>> We thank you very much.
>> 我们非常感谢你。
>> Thank you, >> You need to release the screen for
>> 我们非常感谢你。>> 你需要释放屏幕给
the next speaker.
你需要把屏幕让给下一个发言人。
And while that transition is happening,
在这个过渡期间发生的是，
I'm gonna quickly take advantage to say that, it's not formally yet
我要迅速抓住机会说，这还不是正式的，
but we expect to announce soon that Colorado State University is looking for
但我们预计很快就会宣布科罗拉多州立大学正在寻找
a new junior faculty member in networking.
科罗拉多州立大学正在寻找一位网络领域的新晋助理教授。
So we'll be doing a search this year.
所以我们今年将会进行一次搜索。
So if you're looking for a faculty position,
所以如果你正在寻找一个教职位，
we encourage you to apply to come to lovely four columns.
所以如果你正在寻找一个教职位，我们鼓励你申请来到美丽的四柱城。
So our next speaker is a Laqin Fan,
所以我们的下一位演讲者是Laqin Fan，
who is speaking about Secure Sharing of
所以我们的下一位演讲者是Laqin Fan，他将会讲述关于通过基于名称的访问控制来安全分享时空数据。
Spatial Temporal Data Through Name Based Access Control.
通过基于名称的访问控制来安全分享时空数据。
I'll pass it over to Laqin.
我会把它交给Laqin。
>> Hi everyone, I'm Laqin Fan from University of Memphis.
大家好，我是来自孟菲斯大学的范拉钦。
The topic I'm gonna present is about how we share spatial temporal data
我将要展示的主题是关于我们如何共享时空数据。
security through name based access control.
通过基于名称的访问控制来提供安全性。
Nowadays, mobile devices and sensors are pervasive and provide
如今，移动设备和传感器无处不在，并且提供
the amount of data which are dynamic and continuous on time and the space.
这些数据量是随时间和空间动态且连续的。
For example, mobile has data generated at different times and locations.
例如，移动设备会在不同的时间和地点产生数据。
Those data may contain privacy sensitive information of the user.
这些数据可能包含用户的隐私敏感信息。
We need to make sure only authorized users can access the data,
我们需要确保只有授权的用户才能访问数据，
the challenges are that we need a fine grained access control to express
我们面临的挑战是，我们需要一种精细的访问控制来表达
granular access policies related to time and the location information of the data.
我们需要与时间和数据位置信息相关的精细访问策略。
And we need a real time data sharing to enable our
我们需要实时数据共享以便我们能够
many intervention are based on the collected data.
许多干预措施都是基于收集到的数据。
There is a demo or example of user box data sharing.
这里有一个用户框数据共享的演示或示例。
Bob is using his smartwatch to collect his personal data and
鲍勃正在使用他的智能手表收集个人数据，并且
sharing the data with his coach, physician and data science researcher,
分享数据给他的教练、医生和数据科学研究员，
his coach can access Bob's activity data only generated at the gym, and
他的教练只能访问Bob在健身房产生的活动数据，以及
his physician can access heart rate data between 8 AM to 8 PM.
他的医生可以访问上午8点到晚上8点之间的心率数据。
And data science researcher can access his activity data
数据科学研究员可以访问他的活动数据。
generated during the daytime and not at Bob's house.
在白天生成，而不是在Bob的家里。
Those three consumers have different access policies.
这三个消费者有不同的访问策略。
On your work,
在你的工作中，
we use nimbus access control which is the access control model in India.
我们使用的是Nimbus访问控制，这是印度的访问控制模型。
And NAC provides data confidentiality by encrypting data as a time of production.
NAC通过在数据生成时对其进行加密来保证数据的机密性。
And it also enables end to end security without rely on third party services.
它还能够在不依赖第三方服务的情况下实现端到端的安全性。
As we know, Indian has bunch of benefits
正如我们所知，印度拥有很多好处。
like hierarchical naming structure on data centric security,
像数据中心安全中的分层命名结构，
that is signed the cryptography CLI by the producer and
这是由生产者签名的加密CLI，
nimbus, the data distribution.
Nimbus，数据分发。
Okay, so let me give a brief introduction about how NAC works,
好的，让我简要介绍一下NAC是如何工作的。
NAC models there are three entities Access manager, Producer and Consumer.
NAC模型中有三个实体：访问管理器、生产者和消费者。
And Access Manager publishes access policy as a named public private key pair.
访问管理器以命名的公私钥对的形式发布访问策略。
Whereas public key is used as key encryption key, we call it the KEK here.
而公钥被用作密钥加密密钥，在这里我们称之为KEK。
And the private key is used as key decryption key,
而私钥被用作密钥解密密钥，
we named it KDK, and on data producer generates the data,
我们将其命名为KDK，数据生产者生成数据时，
and there's a corresponding content key, which is a symmetric key.
与之对应的是一个内容密钥，它是一个对称密钥。
To encrypt the data and
为了加密数据并且
retrieve the corresponding KEK to encrypt the content key
检索相应的KEK来加密内容密钥
data consumer, such as the data consumer fetches the encrypted
数据消费者，例如数据消费者获取加密的
content and the encrypted content is key.
内容和加密内容是关键。
And extracts KDK name from the content key name and retrieves the KDK
从内容密钥名称中提取KDK名称，并检索KDK
to decrypt the content key and then use the content key to decrypt the data.
解密内容密钥，然后使用内容密钥来解密数据。
So this is basically the workflow of name based access control.
这基本上是基于名称的访问控制的工作流程。
On your work, we propose spatial temporal access control,
在您的工作中，我们提出了时空访问控制，
which provides a hierarchical naming convention related to time and location.
它提供了一个与时间和地点相关的分层命名约定。
For example, Bob's activity data could be named
例如，Bob的活动数据可以命名为
like Bob/activity/ geolocation/ timestamp.
例如，Bob的活动数据可以命名为地理位置/时间戳。
And our access control could to support granular,
我们的访问控制可以支持细粒度的权限控制，
long real time data sharing so that owners could share historical data in storage.
它还支持长时间的实时数据共享，以便所有者能够共享存储中的历史数据。
It supports granular real time data sharing as well.
它还支持粒度化的实时数据共享。
For example, the physician could retrieve the patient's heart rate data for
例如，医生可以检索病人的心率数据以便及时干预。
timely intervention.
及时干预。
Meanwhile, we can specify different granularities of the content key.
与此同时，我们可以指定内容关键字的不同粒度。
And this granularity could be changed depending on time and location.
而这种粒度可以根据时间和地点进行调整。
For instance, the users could configure content
例如，用户可以配置内容
key to be generated per second, per minute or
每秒、每分钟生成的密钥，或者
at each location based on their needs.
根据他们的需求在每个位置上。
Then how we define granular access policy for
根据他们的需求在每个位置上定义细粒度访问策略，以便业主决定谁可以在哪个粒度访问什么数据。
the owners to decide who can access what data at which granularity.
业主决定谁可以在哪个粒度访问什么数据。
Your design on granular access policy
您关于粒度访问策略的设计
contains a list of constraints like
包含了一系列的限制条件，比如
time interval between 8am to 5pm.
时间间隔为上午8点至下午5点。
Let's say example and spatial area,
例如和空间区域，
which could be at building level, neighborhood level or
它可能处于建筑级别、社区级别或者
city level, for example, users house and city Memphis and
城市级别，例如，用户的房子和城市孟菲斯。
this visual area is represented by even a center point and a radius.
这个可视区域由一个中心点和一个半径来表示。
Here's an example to show a circle to located the building
这是一个示例，用一个圆来定位建筑物。
which is the fitness center at the University of Memphis.
这是孟菲斯大学的健身中心。
We design hierarchical naming scheme for spatial temporal data and
我们为时空数据设计了分层命名方案，并且
as a finger on the right side shows, naming scheme, your tree structure,
我们为时空数据设计了分层命名方案，并且，如右侧所示的手指指出的，你的树状结构，代表了数据所有者的一个可路由的名字前缀。
on data owner represents a routable name prefix of the data.
数据所有者代表了数据的一个可路由的名字前缀。
For example, the University of Memphis and
例如，孟菲斯大学和
the user Bob on data stream refers to the data type,
用户Bob在数据流上指的是数据类型，
like activity and high rate.
像活动和高速率。
Under data streams, there are two sub trees begin with word data and what rate.
在数据流下面，有两个以单词"data"和"what rate"开头的子树。
That sub tree is to represent the namespace for
该子树用于表示命名空间
data, PSync and the content key.
数据、PSync以及内容密钥。
Read sub tree is for namespace of access control.
读取子树用于访问控制的命名空间。
Well, let's see an example how
嗯，让我们来看一个例子如何
abscess policy is specified here.
脓肿政策在这里被指定。
Access manager helps the owner to set up access policies.
访问管理器帮助所有者设置访问策略。
For example, Bob's coach can access Bob's activity data
例如，鲍勃的教练可以访问鲍勃的活动数据。
only generated at fitting fitness center between 8am to 12pm.
仅在上午8点至中午12点间在合身健身中心生成。
From September the 1th to September the 5th every day, and
从9月1日到9月5日，每天，
does a table on the left side is showing the details of the access
左侧的表格显示了访问的详细信息。
policy including the data prefix and the time interval.
策略包括数据前缀和时间间隔。
Indicated by start of the time and end of the time on time unit,
指示的时间单位的开始和结束时间，
which is day here and spatial area specified by
指定的是这里的哪一天和由空间区域指定的，
the center point and the radius also includes.
它还包括中心点和半径。
It includes the consumers prefix, which is the Bob's coach.
它包括消费者前缀，即Bob的教练。
Okay then, let's say how we follow
好吧，那我们来说说我们是如何遵循的。
the naming structure to express access policies.
我们使用命名结构来表达访问策略。
After providing access policies,
在提供访问策略之后，
the Access Manager generates a pair of KEK and KDK.
访问管理器生成一对KEK和KDK。
Their names, she has the same prefix of the data they protect activity.
她们的名字有相同的前缀，这与她们保护的数据活动相关。
Moreover, those keys contain the time and
此外，这些密钥包含时间和~!@#$%^&*()
location constraints by following
遵循位置约束
the access policy previously in that table.
之前在那张表中的访问策略。
And when Bob generates activity data at 8:30 AM September
鲍勃在9月8日早上8:30产生活动数据时，
the first at the fitness center, this data could be named
鲍勃在9月8日早上8:30产生活动数据时，第一次在健身中心，这些数据可以被命名为，包括前缀地理位置和时间戳。
including the prefix geolocation and the timestamp.
包括前缀地理位置和时间戳。
We also let allow Bob to specify content a key granularity,
我们还允许Bob指定内容的关键粒度，
in this case, is one minute.
在这种情况下，是一分钟。
The content of key name also has the same prefix of
关键名的内容也有相同的前缀
the data appending time interval.
数据追加时间间隔。
The range is one minute here, and a special area
这里的范围是一分钟，还有一个特殊区域。
on this content case encrypted using the KEK so
在这种情况下，内容使用KEK进行了加密。
it also contains KEK name prefix.
它还包含了KEK名称前缀。
In some case, the data access will be failed.
在某些情况下，数据访问将会失败。
If the consumer is not granted as the access
如果消费者没有被授予访问权限
permission involves data sharing example,
如果消费者没有被授予访问权限，他的代码只能访问他在健身房生成的活动数据。
his code can only access his activity data generated at gym.
他的代码只能访问他在健身房生成的活动数据。
Even his pouch wants to retrieve Bob's activity data at his house,
即使他的袋子想在他家中检索鲍勃的活动数据，
he will not have the keys to decrypt the data.
他将没有解密数据的钥匙。
We have experiments for data retrieval time for this access control.
我们对这种访问控制的数据检索时间进行了实验。
And we run the experiments in MiniNDN emulation environment
我们在MiniNDN仿真环境中运行了实验。
using a star topology with more than 100 nodes.
我们使用了一个包含100多个节点的星型拓扑。
And our data set contains activity data with continuous time and
我们的数据集包含了具有连续时间的活动数据以及
the different locations.
不同的位置。
And all the consumers have the same access policies.
所有消费者都有相同的访问策略。
>> Cool. >> All right.
>> 很酷。>> 好的。
>> We've reached the end, you're out of time.
>> 我们已经到了最后，你的时间用完了。
>> Okay, so, I would like to finish this slide, please.
>> 好的，那么，我想结束这张幻灯片，请允许。
>> Five seconds.
>> 五秒钟。
>> Okay [LAUGH] >> I'm issuing you two minute warning,
>> 好的 [笑声] >> 我给你们最后两分钟的警告，
so, >> Okay, so in our experiment,
好的，所以在我们的实验中，
we can fake the different granularities of the content key.
我们可以伪造内容关键字的不同粒度。
The granularity could be specified based on data generation interval.
我们可以根据数据生成的间隔来指定粒度。
If the data is generated per second, that granularity could be per second or closer.
如果数据是每秒生成的，那么粒度可以是每秒或者更精细。
And based on the results, there is the trade off between finer
根据结果，存在着在更精细的粒度和生成的竞争者关键字数量之间的权衡。
granularity and the number of contender key generated,
粒度以及生成的竞争者关键字的数量，
the cost of granularity makes one content key cover more data.
粒度的成本使得一个内容密钥覆盖更多数据。
But if the content key is compromised, then those data will be exposed.
但如果内容密钥被破解，那么那些数据就会暴露出来。
And okay, the results.
好的，结果如下。
>> What if you let us leave those up and we'll start with the questions.
>> 如果你让我们保留那些，我们就从问题开始。
>> Okay, so better.
>> 好的，这样更好。
Okay, I would like to say the future work.
好的，我想说一下未来的工作。
The future work are we will specify the spatial areas directly.
未来的工作是我们将直接指定空间区域。
So there was a map, currently it's manually configured.
所以有一张地图，目前是手动配置的。
And we will run experiments by changing the granularity of spatial area.
我们将通过改变空间区域的粒度来进行实验。
Like at the neighborhood level and city level.
像是在社区层面和城市层面。
Apparently, it's fixed at pod network.
显然，它是固定在豆荚网络上的。
>> Okay. >> Okay, that's all, thank you.
>> 好的。 >> 好的，就这些了，谢谢。
>> All right, so we have multiple questions.
>> 好的，所以我们有多个问题。
So how do we encrypt the data that will be used by multiple different access unit.
那么我们如何加密将要被多个不同访问单元使用的数据呢？
So if one piece of data is to be used by say, both a trainer and
那么如果一条数据要同时被例如一个培训师和
a physician at the same data, how is that encrypted?
So if a piece of data needs to be accessed by, for example, a trainer and a physician at the same time, how is that data encrypted?
>> How is the data, >> One piece of data used by
如何对数据进行加密，一个数据同时被使用时，如何进行加密？
two different consumers, whom you're keeping separate?
两个不同的消费者，你是想将他们分开吗？
>> The data is only encrypted by the content key.
>> 数据仅由内容密钥加密。
>> Well, the problem is you get two streams.
>> 好吧，问题是你得到了两个数据流。
That just happened to share some data for a period of time.
这只是恰巧在一段时间内共享了一些数据。
>> It means the same data, right?
>> 这意味着相同的数据，对吗？
>> Same data that shared by two streams that then separate.
>> 两个数据流共享相同的数据，然后分开。
>> Yeah, if it works, there's no problem.
是的，如果它有效，就没有问题。
>> No, let me clarify my question quickly.
不，让我快速澄清我的问题。
So one piece of data used by two groups of people, and
那么，同一份数据被两组人使用，如果这样的话，那么这两组人就有了他们不同的特权。
then these two groups of people have their different privilege.
那么这两组人就有了他们不同的特权。
So if you encrypt the data only once, then one group of people get the C key and
那么如果你只加密一次数据，然后一组人得到了C密钥和
decrypt data.
解密数据。
That means they can also decrypt the data for
这意味着他们也可以解密数据。
the, they can also see the data encrypted for the other.
这意味着他们也可以看到为对方加密的数据。
You see what I mean?
你明白我的意思了吗？
Like Bob activity home TPM is used by both Bob activity home and
Bob活动之家TPM既被Bob活动之家使用，也被
Bob activity, these two groups.
Bob活动之家，这两个团体。
If there's only one C key, that means both group have used the same C key.
如果只有一个C键，那意味着这两个团体使用的是同一个C键。
I mean, my question is, do you need to encrypt the data for twice or
我是说，我的问题是，你需要对数据加密两次吗还是
two groups because they have different privilege.
两个组因为他们有不同的权限。
>> No, even those two groups, they have issued access
不，即使是那两个组，他们已经发放了访问权限。
permission, as soon as they can access the data.
他们一旦能够访问数据，就有了权限。
It means the two groups, they want to share the content of key with each other.
这意味着两个团队，他们想要相互分享关键内容。
And then we don't, >> They don't, their distinct.
然后我们不会，>> 他们不会，他们是不同的。
>> Even they don't share the content key and if they are issued as
即使他们不共享内容密钥，如果他们被发放为
a stem access policy, I think they can access the data in any way.
即使他们不共享内容密钥，如果他们被发放为一个茎干访问策略，我认为他们可以以任何方式访问数据。
>> Okay, sounds like we should discuss this more on the chat group.
>> 好的，听起来我们应该在聊天群里更多地讨论这个问题。
So, another question is, given this naming policy,
那么，另一个问题是，在这个命名政策下，
it sounds as if the consumer can learn when and
它听起来像是消费者可以了解何时以及在这个命名政策下，where data was generated even if they can't decrypt it.
where data was generated even if they can't decrypt it.
即使他们无法解密数据，也能了解数据是在何处产生的。
And doesn't that actually reveal a fair bit about where somebody is and
而这实际上不就揭示了某人所在的位置和
what they're doing.
他们正在做的事情。
But can you local, right?
但你可以本地化，对吗？
>> Even it is repeated as a question?
即使这是一个重复的问题？
>> Okay, that's also in the chat group if you want it, from Dave Moran.
>> 好的，如果你需要，这也在聊天群里，来自Dave Moran。
Given your naming scheme as I understand it and
根据我所理解的你的命名方案以及
Dave, I'm aligning your question slightly.
戴夫，我稍微调整了一下你的问题。
The consumer of the data can still see the name even if they can't decrypt
数据的消费者即使无法解密，仍然可以看到名称
the content.
内容。
And the question is,
这个问题是，
does the name alone give away enough to localize a person in time and space?
这个名字本身就足以确定一个人在时间和空间中的位置吗？
So I would know where you were even if you didn't know the exact readings.
所以即使你不知道确切的读数，我也会知道你在哪里。
>> Okay, this time I was standing, I think it means that data name,
>> 好的，这次我站着，我认为这意味着数据名称，
the data consumers, they don't know the data names to retrieve the data.
数据消费者，并不知道用来检索数据的数据名称。
>> No, they tell them they're able to discover the names.
不，他们告诉他们能够发现这些名称。
Sorry, Dave, you wanna try?
抱歉，Dave，你想试试吗？
>> Or I can jump in.
>> 或者我可以加入进来。
>> Sorry, if the names contain location and time in the actual names.
>> 抱歉，如果实际名称中包含了地点和时间。
I assume the consumer can use a nice a guessing strategy to try and
我假设消费者可以使用一个不错的猜测策略来尝试并且
find which names exist and which names don't.
找出哪些名字是存在的，哪些名字是不存在的。
And they'll ultimately by picking a name get a hit,
他们最终会通过选择一个名字而找到线索，
from which they know anything that the name itself tells them.
他们从中知道了名字本身告诉他们的任何事情。
Even if they can't decrypt the data,
即使他们无法解密数据，
they can't get a key to decrypt the data that was stored under that name.
即使他们无法获取密钥来解密存储在那个名称下的数据。
So the question is, are these names that have geolocation information and
所以问题是，这些带有地理位置信息的名称是否
easily guessable, another way to ask the question.
容易被猜到的，换一种方式提问这个问题。
>> For the sake of time, if I can jump in,
>> 为了节省时间，如果我可以插一句，
I think this is a question touched upon during our panel earlier today.
我认为这是我们今天早些时候在小组讨论中提到的一个问题。
The fundamental is how much information gets exposed through the naming.
基本原则是通过命名暴露了多少信息。
I think my answer adequate at that time is that it's all about how
我认为我当时的回答是充分的，就是这一切都取决于怎样
one can obscure the names, right?
可以隐藏这些名字，对吗？
The only thing the names need to be known is by the producers and consumers.
只有生产者和消费者需要知道这些名字。
If they have a means of understanding the means to
如果他们有了解方法的方法
obscure the name, that's all you needed.
模糊名称，这就是你所需要的。
>> But you can't tell a good consumer from a bad consumer until after they try to
>> 但你无法在他们尝试之前分辨出一个好消费者和坏消费者。
access something.
访问某物。
>> I thought consumer right was pre defined.
>> 我以为消费者权利是预先定义好的。
>> Okay, so again, another topic, I think, for the chat, since we need to move along.
>> 好的，再次提醒，我认为这是聊天中另一个话题，因为我们需要继续进行。
Thank you Lixia for your talk, and if you could release the screen for Mohammed,
谢谢丽霞的发言，如果你能把屏幕让给穆罕默德，
that would be wonderful.
那会很棒。
So our last talk of the session Is by Mohammed Elbadri.
所以我们这个环节的最后一个报告是由Mohammed Elbadri进行的。
And Mohammed is a third year PhD student at Stony Brook University.
穆罕默德是纽约州立大学石溪分校的一名三年级博士研究生。
And his research interests are wireless networks, so he's being more
穆罕默德的研究兴趣是无线网络，所以他在这方面更加专注。
specific about his research interests here, and edge communication.
因此，我预计在他的演讲中，我们将听到他在这些研究兴趣方面的一些内容，特别是关于边缘通信的部分。
So I expect we'll hear about some aspects of those interests in his talk,
因此，我预计在他的演讲中，我们将听到他在这些研究兴趣方面的一些内容，
which is entitled A Full Data-centric Network Stack Integrating V-MAC and NFD.
题为“整合V-MAC和NFD的全数据中心网络栈”。
So Mohammed, you're up.
所以穆罕默德，轮到你了。
>> Thank you, can you see my screen?
>> 谢谢，你们能看到我的屏幕吗？
>> Yes, we can see your screen just fine, thank you.
>> 是的，我们能很清楚地看到你的屏幕，谢谢。
>> Sounds good, thank you.
>> 好的，谢谢。
So I'll be covering full data centric stack integration between V-MAC and NFD.
所以我将负责V-MAC和NFD之间的全数据中心堆栈集成。
V-MAC is a new phase we're integrating with NFD.
V-MAC是我们正在与NFD集成的新阶段。
And V-MAC is a wireless medium access control layer,
V-MAC是一个无线介质访问控制层，
designed completely from scratch which is completely data centric.
设计得完全从零开始，完全以数据为中心。
The reason we ended up designing a data centric MAC
我们最终设计了一个以数据为中心的MAC的原因是因为现有的MAC层有多个方面的不足。
is because existing MAC layers fall short for multiple reasons.
是因为现有的MAC层在多个方面存在不足。
One of them is the network and
之一是网络和
discovery procedure must be established before any data centric communication.
在任何以数据为中心的通信之前，必须建立发现程序。
There is a beaconed communication and
在信标通信中，
sharing that is address space that must happen.
必须发生的是地址空间的共享。
Given an ad hoc network, you must join the network before any communication occur.
在一个临时网络中，你必须在任何通信发生之前加入网络。
That incurs continuous overhead, media neutralization and latency,
这会导致持续的开销、媒体中和以及延迟，
specifically in mobile environments.
特别是在移动环境中。
The destination must be determined before transmission.
在传输之前必须确定目的地。
That's the standard address based communication destination and
这是基于地址的标准通信目的地和
network group.
这是基于地址的标准通信目的地和网络组。
And traditional MAC multicast support doesn't exist.
传统的MAC多播支持并不存在。
In general its broadcast if we're using ad hoc communication which
通常情况下，如果我们使用的是自组织通信，那么它就是广播形式。
is at low base rate, at low data rate, one or six Mbps.
是在低基础速率下，即低数据速率，1或6 Mbps。
And if we go higher data rates, it ends up being very lossy.
如果我们提高数据速率，最终会导致很高的丢包率。
So the challenges we face by designing a new wireless MAC layer is that there's
因此，我们在设计新的无线MAC层时面临的挑战是存在着
a varying reception quality of different neighboring receivers.
不同邻近接收器的接收质量各异。
And in general it's very lossy,
一般来说，它的损耗很大，
I believe some presenters from the previous presentations touched upon that.
我相信之前的一些报告者已经提到过这个问题了。
And in general from highly mobile environments like vehicular networks,
在一般情况下，来自高度移动的环境，比如车载网络，
we have very short contact durations that we want to share data in between.
我们有非常短暂的接触时间，我们希望在这期间共享数据。
However, in wireless, that is wireless communication, we have broadcast meter.
然而，在无线通信中，我们有广播仪表。
So we can do multicast very easily, which works very well with an NFDM MDM.
因此我们可以非常容易地进行多播，这与NFDM MDM非常匹配。
We also have the potential to eliminate network discovery,
我们还有可能消除网络发现，
which is joining a network, and rely on attribute data filtering.
它能够加入一个网络，并依靠属性数据过滤。
And that's why we designed V-MAC,
这就是我们设计V-MAC的原因，
which is a new wireless MAC layer designed from scratch which is data centric.
这是一种从零开始设计的新型无线MAC层，它是以数据为中心的。
The system is beaconless, It doesn't require any discovery or
该系统无需信标，它不需要任何发现或加入网络的过程，因此消除了巨大的开销。
joining a network, so it eliminates a huge overhead.
加入网络，因此消除了巨大的开销。
You turn on the radio and you can communicate and share data right away.
打开无线电，你就可以立即进行通信和数据共享。
It uses a pending encoding table which does the data name filtering In the MAC
它使用一个待处理的编码表来进行MAC中的数据名称过滤。
layer.
层。
We do one matching, it's not pending interest table, it's encoding.
我们进行一次匹配，这不是待处理的兴趣表，而是编码。
And the reasons is because in ICM layer, it's one interest, one data packet.
在ICM层中，原因是因为一次兴趣对应一份数据包。
However, in MAC layer,
但是，在MAC层中，
it's one interest to multiple frames that correspond to one packet.
它是将一个数据包对应到多个帧中的一种兴趣。
A packet gets fragmented and
一个数据包被分段后
then we filter based on data name multiple fragments.
然后我们根据数据名称过滤多个片段。
And we also build the best effort control last robust multicast system.
我们还构建了最佳尽力控制的最后鲁棒多播系统。
And that protocol doesn't require any setup,
该协议不需要任何设置，
doesn't require any during communication or creating a multicast group name or
不需要在通信过程中或创建多播组名称时进行任何设置，
similar systems that exist in traditional MAC.
传统MAC中存在的类似系统。
And it provides low control losses among all receivers,
并且在所有接收器中提供了较低的控制损耗，
we tested up to 15 receivers.
我们测试了多达15个接收器。
We have the paper that discusses in detail exact implementation and
我们有一篇论文，详细讨论了确切的实现方式以及
the protocol design that is going to appear in SEC 20, and
协议设计将出现在SEC 20中，以及
the name is at the bottom in the footnote.
名字在脚注的最底部。
To show the performance of V-MAC as a face being used for NFD,
为了展示V-MAC作为NFD面部使用的性能，
we have a testbed which uses Raspberry Pi's and use V alpha dongles,
我们有一个测试平台，它使用树莓派并且使用V alpha无线电调制解调器，
which are commodity dongles off the shelf, pretty cheap and anyone can attain them.
它们是市面上常见的、价格便宜的无线电调制解调器，任何人都可以轻易购得。
We're in the third iteration of the kernel module,
我们正在进行内核模块的第三次迭代，
which is provisioned for the NFD integration.
它是为NFD集成配置的。
I'm going to ask Kevin to play a video shortly right after.
我一会儿就让凯文播放一个视频。
This video is basically one producer and
这个视频基本上是一个制作人和……
ten consumers requesting the same video at the same time.
十个消费者同时请求同一个视频。
We're transmitting at 54 Mbps, the video is around 2 MB of duration.
我们的传输速率是54 Mbps，视频大约2 MB大小。
Kevin if you can kindly please play the video
凯文，如果可以的话，请播放视频。
Thank you, so as you saw earlier, an ad hoc out of ten receivers,
谢谢，正如你之前看到的，临时的十个接收器中，
this was broadcast out of ten receivers, only two were able to even play the file.
在十个接收器中，只有两个能够播放该文件。
And the two had very high losses at 68% and the other one was much higher.
在这两个接收器中，一个损失非常高，达到了68%，而另一个的损失更是高得多。
Meanwhile, in V-MAC, it was very controlled low loss for
与此同时，在V-MAC中，损失非常低，得到了很好的控制。
all ten receivers, 0.5% and lower 0.2%.
所有十个接收器，0.5%及以下降至0.2%。
We also have done further experiments, we've done stationary experiments.
我们还进行了进一步的实验，我们进行了静态实验。
We tried from 3 consumers up to 15 consumers for ad hoc and multicast.
我们尝试了从3个消费者到15个消费者的临时广播和多点传送。
For ad hoc broadcasts, as you can see on the left side on the left figure,
在左图的左侧可以看到，对于临时广播，
you'll have b3, which is three consumers one producer, 5, 7, 10, 15.
您将拥有b3，即三个消费者一个生产者，5、7、10、15。
And then after the multicast with V-MAC robustness protocol results.
然后在采用V-MAC鲁棒性协议的多播结果之后。
Broadcasts with ad hoc across all receivers,
在所有接收器中进行临时广播，
there is always between 40 to 60%.
在所有接收器中进行临时广播，百分之四十到六十的比例始终存在，同时，当我们切换到V-MAC时，我们始终能保持低于5%的一致性。
Meanwhile, when we switch to V-MAC, we get under 5% consistently across the board.
同时，当我们切换到V-MAC时，我们始终能保持低于5%的一致性。
We've also done real vehicle experiments where we have four consumers
我们还进行了真实车辆实验，在实验中我们有四个消费者。
in platoon and one producer using 54 Mbps data rate again.
在车队中，还有一名生产者使用54 Mbps的数据传输速率。
The speed was moderate speed 25 to 35 Mbps and it was distance was around four miles.
速度是中等速度，大约25到35 Mbps，距离大约四英里。
And we've tried multiple interests and
我们尝试了多种兴趣点，
data can be transmitted packets includes 500 data frames the interests coming back.
数据可以传输包括500个数据帧的数据包，这些是返回的兴趣点。
As you can see on the right figure, the loss rates is controlled, less than 15%.
如您在右图中看到的，丢包率得到控制，低于15%。
Even receiver number 4, which went out of range multiple times,
即使是多次超出范围的接收器4，
it was still able to keep controlled loss rate.
它仍然能够保持受控的丢失率。
When we tried to do ad hoc with the same experiment, it didn't work well.
当我们尝试用同样的实验来做临时的安排时，效果并不好。
Because receiver number 4 and
由于接收器4和~!@#$%^&*()
receiver number 3 kept running out of network as the beacon kept timing out.
接收器3不断脱离网络，因为信标不断超时。
And it kept joining and leaving in network which didn't work out for
它不断地加入和脱离网络，但这并没有奏效。
receiving any data.
未能接收到任何数据。
Thus integration of V between V-MAC and using V-MAC as a face of NFD,
因此将V与V-MAC集成，并使用V-MAC作为NFD的界面，
the benefits is that we get a full data-centric stack.
我们获得了一个完整的数据中心化技术栈。
We get a controlled loss rate, instead of 10 to 90% varying loss in broadcasts,
我们获得了一个可控的丢包率，而不是在广播中变化的10到90%的丢包率。
we'll get 1 to 5% multicast Loss rates for stationary in less than 15% for
我们将获得1到5%的多播丢包率，对于静止的情况下少于15%的
mobile environments.
移动环境。
Our latency is not that high.
我们的延迟并不高。
It's less than 2.5 times of broadcast transmission.
它不到广播传输的2.5倍。
So if you take 10 seconds in broadcast, it will take
大约25秒，风险最大，说V-MAC是15个接收器的多播控制损失。
We have the cross stack latency improvement, which comes from a software
我们实现了跨栈延迟的改善，这来自于软件
system that we integrated all the way from the firmware up to the user space.
我们将系统集成了，从固件一直到用户空间。
We improve the transmission cross stack latency 60 times, and
我们将跨栈传输的延迟提高了60倍，并且
the reception by 100 times, we also made the system interoperable was ad-hoc and
我们将接收能力提高了100倍，同时也使系统具备了即席网络的互操作性，并且
can co-exist with any regular WiFi for adaptability over the environment.
可以与任何常规WiFi共存，以适应不同环境。
We support high data rates.
我们支持高数据传输速率。
Just for time sake, don't rush this a little for NFD face.
为了节省时间，不要急于为NFD面部处理这个问题。
We provide three different media types,
我们提供三种不同的媒体类型，
which is interest data and announcement, which is being used for NACK.
我们提供的兴趣数据和公告正在被用于NACK。
We also provide a system that's called implicit interest.
我们还提供了一个称为隐性兴趣的系统。
What implicit interest is, is an internal subscription.
隐性兴趣是一种内部订阅。
Because V-MAC right now filters based on data name or attributes.
因为V-MAC目前根据数据名称或属性进行过滤。
If you don't subscribe to the data, it will not forward it to NFT.
如果你不订阅数据，它不会将数据转发给NFT。
So if someone wants to subscribe to data without sending an interest,
所以如果有人想订阅数据而不发送兴趣，
you can use an implicit answers.
您可以使用隐式回答。
We also have configurable data rates, on one to 65 MPs at ages 8 to 11.
我们还有可配置的数据速率，适用于8至11岁的儿童，从1到65 MPs。
And that platform is ready for Raspberry Pi, and up to 900 MPs on 8 to 11 ac
该平台已经适用于Raspberry Pi，并且支持8至11ac的高达900 MPs的数据速率。
which runs on Jetson using mini PCIE adaptive that's their Wi-Fi chip.
该设备在Jetson上运行，使用mini PCIE适配器，那是他们的Wi-Fi芯片。
One of our future work is to finalize integration prepare for code reviews,
我们未来的工作之一是完成集成准备，为代码审查做好准备，
and testing.
和测试。
The code will be available to the community in October.
代码将于10月份提供给社区。
We need some help from the community to finalize integration, and
我们需要社区的帮助来完成集成，以及
verify that our integration is complete and successful.
验证我们的集成是否完整且成功。
We can also provide the source code for V-MAC.
我们还可以提供V-MAC的源代码。
If anyone is interested, just contact me right away and we can provide it.
如果有人感兴趣，请立即联系我，我们可以提供。
We're also working on multicast frame rate adaptation,
我们还在研究多播帧率自适应技术，
to adapt the data rate instead of having a fixed rate which will improve the latency,
以适应数据速率而不是固定速率，这将改善延迟，
robustness, and also reduce some of the loss rates.
以提高鲁棒性，并且还能减少一些丢包率。
Further, we're also working on supporting more hardware
此外，我们还在努力支持更多的硬件设备。
chips to support more different Wi-Fi dongles, which also can work on Android.
芯片支持更多不同的Wi-Fi适配器，这些适配器也可以在Android上使用。
We have also new interesting data centric research problems like producer selection
我们还面临着一些新的、有趣的以数据为中心的研究问题，比如生产者选择。
can be done in a different way where instead of the producer deciding
可以用另一种方式来做，不是由生产者来决定
which producer to send the data, we can have all producers send the data, and
我们可以让所有的生产者发送数据，以及
then through the medium while the transmission is happening,
然后通过媒介在传输过程中，
the consumer selects which producers ideal for them which works very well.
消费者选择最适合他们的生产者，这样做非常有效。
It could show promising results in mobile environments, where the dynamic of
它在移动环境中可能显示出有希望的结果，其中动态特性需要
the links change consistently, and it needs to be adapted dynamically.
链路持续变化，需要进行动态适配。
And also Data-centric they can use.
他们也可以使用以数据为中心的方法。
Thank you so much Lixia Zhang and Asavari Limaye for your support and
非常感谢张丽霞和Asavari Limaye的支持，以及
starting efforts between integration for NFD and V-MAC, and
开始努力将NFD和V-MAC进行整合，以及
I'm happy to take any of your questions.
我很乐意回答你们的任何问题。
>> So I notice you're basically pushing us all to go read a paper that's going to
>> 所以我注意到你基本上是在鼓励我们都去阅读一篇将会在11月出现的关于V-MAC的论文。
appear in November about V-MAC.
将会在11月出现的关于V-MAC的。
On the other hand, you say that it's a software implementation.
另一方面，你说这是一个软件实现。
So it just works on an existing Wi-Fi interface.
所以它只能在现有的Wi-Fi接口上工作。
Is that correct?
这是正确的吗？
Or have you.
或者你有？
>> Right, We made >> Yeah
对，我们确保了系统是关闭的 >> 是的
>> We made sure the system is working off
我们确保了系统是关闭的。
the shelf commodity Wi-Fi dongles, so anyone in the research community can
货架上的商品Wi-Fi适配器，因此研究社区中的任何人都可以
use it right away without buying expensive hardware customizing hardware.
立即使用它，而无需购买昂贵的硬件定制硬件。
It's pretty much we change the firmware and SOC on the chip and
我们基本上是更改了芯片上的固件和SOC，以及
the kernel stack completely.
我们彻底更改了内核栈。
The way we eliminated the whole outerspace MAC layer.
我们彻底消除了整个外层空间的MAC层。
>> Okay, so you have it that year, you're transmitting the Wi-Fi band, but
好的，所以那一年你们正在传输Wi-Fi频段，但是
you're doing something very different.
你们在做一些非常不同的事情。
>> Right.
对，好的。
>> Right, okay, and
对，好的，以及
what you've done is you've done some of your mapped channels or
你所做的是你已经映射了一些频道或者
particular frequencies to names are you doing simply, are you varying on the,
你所做的是你已经映射了一些频道或者特定的频率到名称上，你是在变化上做的简单吗？还是在...上有所变化？
I mean, the obvious way to do a lot of what you're doing is to do some of
我是说，你所做的很多事情的明显方法是去做一些...
the shared random shared clock approaches, that have been done for
这些已经进行过的共享随机共享时钟方法，
military ad-hoc networks, so when to wake up to talk with different people, and
军事临时网络，那么何时唤醒以与不同的人交谈，以及
there's no access or join and leave that has happened.
没有发生过访问、加入或离开的情况。
It's just all clock based, is yours clock based or
它完全是基于时钟的，你的是基于时钟的还是？
is it some or is it based on NDN names?
它是基于NDN名称的还是基于其他的？
Or is it using some other method for deciding who gets to talk when to whom.
它是使用其他什么方法来决定谁何时与谁通话吗？
>> We're actually relying on CSMA as though,
我们实际上依赖CSMA，好像，
we kept CSMA as though it's much random access.
我们保持了CSMA，好像它是非常随机的访问方式。
>> Okay, and cool.
>> 好的，很酷。
>> Thank you.
>> 谢谢。
>> See, I think we have time for one more question if somebody wants to put one up
>> 看，我认为如果有人想提出问题的话，我们还有时间再回答一个问题。
in the chat room, otherwise, I'll end the session here.
在聊天室里，否则，我就在这里结束会话。
Mohammed, that was a fun talk.
穆罕默德，那是一次愉快的交谈。
Thank you. >> Thank you so much.
谢谢。 >> 非常感谢。
>> All right.
>> 好的。
Thank you very much.
非常感谢。
I think that's it.
我想就是这样。
>> Okay, thank you very much, Craig.
>> 好的，非常感谢你，Craig。
Our next session is on discovery and configuration.
我们下一环节是关于发现和配置。
And Marie Joseph Merpati
是康卡迪亚大学的兼职教授，并将主持这一环节。
So go ahead manages it.
他将负责管理这一环节。
>> Okay, great.
>> 好的，太好了。
Hey.
嘿。
So, yeah, so we'll come to this last but not least session,
所以，是的，我们将进入这最后一个但同样重要的环节，
where we're looking at Discovery, which I think is extremely important.
所以，是的，我们将进入这最后一个但同样重要的环节，在这里我们将探讨发现，我认为这是极其重要的。
Actually, it's important for me, I hope it's important for the people and
实际上，这对我来说很重要，我希望它对人们也同样重要，
everything we do when there's data-centric systems.
我们所做的一切都是围绕数据为中心的系统。
The first talk is from John Della Version who is
第一场演讲是由John Della Version进行的。
a second year PhD student at UCLA working with Lixia.
一位在加州大学洛杉矶分校与Lixia合作的二年级博士研究生。
He is a true Los Angelenos born and raised in Los Angeles.
他是一个地道的洛杉矶人，在洛杉矶出生并长大。
And he got his undergraduate degree in physics and
他在物理学专业获得了本科学位，
computer science from Amherst, which is close to me now.
他在阿默斯特获得了计算机科学专业的学位，这个学校离我现在的位置很近。
And so yes, what's California and Massachusetts getting together and
与此同时，加利福尼亚州和马萨诸塞州在一起......
discovering something with MDN.
在MDN上发现了一些东西。
So go ahead, John.
那就开始吧，约翰。
>> Great time [CROSSTALK] >> I'll time verybody at 10 minutes.
>> [同时讲话] >> 我会给每个人计时10分钟。
So try to give time for questions.
所以请尽量留出时间来回答问题。
So again, thank you, John.
所以再次感谢你，约翰。
Please go ahead.
请继续。
>> Hi, everyone.
>> 大家好。
Thank you so much for coming to the talk on MDN plug and play.
非常感谢大家来参加MDN即插即用的讲座。
The work itself was done by Eric Newbery, can you please ping me and
作品本身是由Eric Newbery完成的，请给我发消息。
Lixia and as you know, the presenter is drawn to lamberson.
The work itself was completed by Eric Newbery, please message me. So with that in mind, a natural question you might have is why the presenter is attracted to Lamberson.
So with that in mind, a natural question you might have
所以考虑到这一点，你可能会自然而然地产生一个问题。
given the name of the talk is what is plug and play.
考虑到这个演讲的名称是什么是即插即用。
So we're going to go ahead and
那我们就继续进行吧。
for the purposes of this talk did cut that into two sections.
为了这次演讲的目的，我把它分成了两部分。
So first configuration, this is the plug notion.
所以首先是配置，这是所谓的插头概念。
This is the setup that one requires to actually talk to other nodes
这是必需的设置，以便实际与其他节点通信。
on the network.
在网络上。
And secondly, we have the plane ocean, which is reachability.
其次，我们有平面海洋，即可达性。
How do you find the other nodes on the network?
您如何在网络上找到其他节点？
How do you find who you'd like to talk to?
您如何找到您想要交谈的人？
And in this talk, we want to compare these goals, or
在这次讨论中，我们希望比较这些目标，或者
compare these two steps between IP and NDN.
比较这两个步骤在IP和NDN之间的差异。
Ideally define some sort of steps in NDN for how we do this and
理想情况下，在NDN中定义一些步骤来说明我们如何做这件事，并且
learn something from that.
从中学到一些东西。
So with that in mind, yes, great.
所以抱着这样的想法，是的，很好。
So we'll first start off with IP configuration, so the goal of IP
所以我们首先从IP配置开始，IP配置的目标是
configuration is very simply connectivity to the global Internet.
配置的目的非常简单，就是要实现与全球互联网的连接。
And in this sort of plug notion,
在这种插入的概念中，
you plug a node into an existing connected IP infrastructure or
您将一个节点插入到现有的连接IP基础设施中，或者
some semi fixed topology, with the goal of being able to talk to other nodes that
一些半固定的拓扑结构，其目的是能够与其他节点进行通信，这些节点
are, plugged in and connected to that infrastructure or just topology.
是接入并连接到该基础设施或仅仅是拓扑结构的。
And if we wanted to visualize it, we could imagine within the larger internet,
如果我们想要将其形象化，我们可以想象在更大的互联网之中，
some narrow slice.
一些狭窄的切片。
We have some nodes,
我们有一些节点，
they have arbitrary IP addresses that are connected to some set of routers.
它们具有任意的IP地址，并连接到一些路由器集。
And in order to actually join the network,
为了实际加入网络，
a new node must connect to some DHCP server, retrieve an IP address,
为了实际加入网络，一个新节点必须连接到某个DHCP服务器，检索一个IP地址，
your subnet mask, your default gateway, maybe a DNS server.
你的子网掩码、默认网关，可能还有一个DNS服务器。
Then once that's connected, once you've gotten those four things,
那么一旦连接上了，一旦你得到了这四样东西，
the configuration is complete, you're connected.
配置完成后，你就连接上了。
you can communicate with other nodes within the network.
你就可以和网络内的其他节点进行通信。
And then because IP is just about connectivity,
然后因为IP只是关于连接性，
everything involving trust is necessarily going to happen on some higher layer.
一切涉及信任的事务都必然会发生在更高的层次上。
Which can introduce both vulnerabilities and some missed opportunities,
这可能会引入一些漏洞并错失一些机会，
because you can't know if you're talking to the right party over just IP.
因为仅凭IP地址，你无法确定自己是否在和正确的对方通话。
And the type of vulnerability that I'd like to illustrate, is a DDoS attack.
我想要说明的一种漏洞类型是DDoS攻击。
You can spoof the source address, you can do
你可以伪造源地址，你可以做到
redirect attacks pretending that you've someone else, so on and so forth.
重定向攻击假装你是别人，等等。
Because you have no way to verify authenticity on this level, and
因为在这个层面上，你无法验证真实性，而且
that can sort of lead to a lot of damage as we've all seen.
这可能会导致很多损害，正如我们都见证过的那样。
And secondly, we've seen the example of missed opportunities here, where you would
而第二，我们在这里见证了错失良机的例子，那种你本可以……
really like to have infrastructure that's designed around talking.
真的很喜欢围绕交谈设计的基础设施。
On the edge between two relatively local nodes or host, but you can't,
位于两个相对本地节点或主机的边缘，但你不能，
because you don't have a way to verify authenticity.
因为你没有办法去验证真实性。
And so this sort of leads to a lot of missed opportunities, or
因此，这种情况往往导致了很多错失的机会，或者
going to the cloud for everything or what have you.
因此，这种情况往往导致了很多错失的机会，或者对于所有事情都上云等等。So with that in mind, we can sort of briefly talk about the play of notion,
So with that in mind, we can sort of briefly talk about the play of notion,
因此，考虑到这一点，我们可以简要地谈谈概念的运用。
IP reachability, ultimately this is fairly trivial.
IP可达性，归根结底这是相当简单的。
Once you've actually done your configuration,
配置完成后，
once you can talk to everyone, you either send it to the local network or
一旦你能和每个人通信，你要么将其发送到本地网络，要么
you send it to your default gateway.
你将其发送到默认网关。
And the network takes care of getting it to the right place or the right host.
网络会负责将其送达正确的地点或正确的主机。
So finally, we can move on to what is perhaps the more interesting notion,
所以最终，我们可以继续探讨或许更有趣的概念，
NDN configuration.
NDN配置。
So, if IP configuration is plugging a host into a fixed infrastructure or
那么，如果IP配置是将主机接入固定基础设施，或者
semi fixed infrastructure.
半固定基础设施。
NDN configuration is plugging a new entity into an application namespace.
NDN配置是将新实体插入应用程序命名空间中。
And because trust relations exists within application namespaces, there
由于应用程序命名空间内存在信任关系，因此
are also inheriting trust relations within that namespace, relative to other names.
我们也在该命名空间内继承了与其他名称相关的信任关系。
And it's important to note here, that because we're asserting trust here,
需要特别指出的是，因为我们在这里建立信任，
because we're bootstrapping both names and security, authenticity here is critical.
因为我们在这里同时启动名称和安全性，真实性至关重要。
If you sort of screw that up, you are paused for the rest of the process.
如果你稍微搞砸了，那你就得在接下来的过程中暂停。
But as I said, this configuration process is all about names and security.
但正如我所说，这个配置过程全都关乎命名和安全性。
And in fact, the whole configuration process,
实际上，整个配置过程，
can be encapsulated in, first, getting a name from some relevant application.
可以被封装在首先，从某个相关应用程序获取一个名称中。其次，从信任锚点获取证书。
And secondly, getting a certificate from a trust anchor.
其次，从信任锚点获取证书。
Everything else is either automatable,
其他一切都是可以自动化的，
you can retrieve a trust anchor from a trust schema.
您可以从信任模式中检索一个信任锚点。
Excuse me, from that trust anchor for reachability,
You can retrieve a trust anchor from the trust model.
you can automatically discover namespaces.
你可以自动发现命名空间。
And it's also interesting to note that NDN configuration,
值得注意的是，NDN配置，
sort of unlike IP configuration, is not a one time thing.
有别于IP配置，这不是一次性的事情。
An NDN entity that's on the network, can in fact get a new certificate or
一个在网络上的NDN实体，实际上可以获得一个新的证书或者
even get a new name or so on and so forth.
甚至还可以获得一个新的名称等等。
Which we haven't explored within the code that you've developed, but
我们还没有在你开发的代码中探索过的是，但是
use sort of part of NDN configuration.
使用某种NDN配置的一部分。
And of course, the fact that you're involved in application namespaces,
当然，你参与的是应用命名空间，
rather than in infrastructure or topology.
相比之下，在基础设施或拓扑结构方面。
Is also what makes NDN so
也是使得NDN如此
good at accommodating mobility with this configuration.
擅长使用这种配置适应移动性。
Because you don't need to get a new certificate every time you move places, or
因为你每次搬地方时都不需要重新获得证书，或者
change the router or whatever that you're connected to.
更换你所连接的路由器或其他相关设备。
So if we wanted to sort of visualize NDN configuration,
因此，如果我们想要直观地了解NDN配置，
we might take, again, some small sample or some small network.
我们可能会再次选取一些小样本或一些小型网络。
Where we have a couple of hosts that have sort of example, trust schemas.
在这里，我们有一些主机，它们有一些类似示例的信任模式。
And then two trust anchors, in this case we've two different namespaces/ndn/home.
然后有两个信任锚点，在这种情况下我们有两个不同的命名空间/ndn/home。
So if a new entity wants to join the network, all it has to do, or what it has
因此，如果一个新实体想要加入网络，它所需要做的，或者它必须做的，就是首先从它运行的那种应用程序中获取一个名称。
to do, is first get a name from the sort of application that it's running.
所需要做的，或者它必须做的，就是首先从它运行的那种应用程序中获取一个名称。
And then get a certificate from the anchor,
然后从锚点获取一个证书，
if it wants to publish under the namespace /home/p or the prefix /home/p.
如果它想要在命名空间/home/p下或前缀/home/p下发布。
They would have to get a certificate from the trust anchor 2,
他们必须从信任锚2处获得一个证书，
which sort of runs administrates/home.
它在某种程度上运行管理家庭。
And if you'd like me to linger on the slide,
如果你想让我在幻灯片上停留一会儿，
I'll come back to it, please just let me know.
如果你想要我回到那个话题，请告诉我。
But, from here we're sort of taking care of the plug aspect
但是，从这里开始，我们就要处理好插头方面的问题了。
of NDN configuration, and we can get to the play aspect.
但是，从这里开始，我们就要处理好插头方面的问题了。接下来就是 NDN 配置的好处之一，我们可以开始进行实际操作了。
And one of the nice things about NDN,
而NDN的好处之一，
is there are many ways to get reachability here.
这里有很多方法可以实现可达性。
Once you have done the essential components of configuration, you can
一旦你完成了配置的基本组件，你就可以
either use NDN broadcast self-learning to figure out where other namespaces are.
或者使用NDN广播自学习来确定其他命名空间的位置。
You could use NDND, you could use Ndn-autoconfig,
您可以使用NDND，也可以使用Ndn-autoconfig，
which contrary [LAUGH] to the name, is not actually an auto-configuration system.
与名称相反，它实际上并不是一个自动配置系统。[笑]
It's a fine closest hub system, so
它是一个很好的最近集线器系统，所以
that's definitely falls under the category of reachability.
这显然属于可达性范畴。
Or you could use NLSR for routing and
或者你可以使用NLSR进行路由选择。
then, There we go.
那么，我们开始吧。
So from there, we can ask the question, how do you implement plug and play, or
那么，从那里我们可以提出这个问题，如何实现即插即用，或者说，有哪些方法可以做到这一点？
what ways to do that, that are there to do that?
有哪些方法可以做到这一点？有哪些方式可以实现呢？
And to our view, probably the best way to do that is to
而在我们看来，实现这一点的最佳方式可能是
provide easy ways to safe way, which means authentically here.
提供简单安全的方式，这里指的是真实可靠的方式。
Input a trust anchor, certificate, name of the band, and
输入一个信任锚点、证书、乐队名称，以及
then do our best to automate all the reachability beyond that.
然后尽我们所能自动化所有超出此范围的可达性。
This is sort of our imagining of how you replicate the system of, in IP land.
这在某种程度上是我们想象中的如何在IP领域复制该系统。
Connecting to the internet, doing DHCP and
连接到互联网，进行动态主机配置协议（DHCP）操作，然后就准备好随时插上即可使用。
then just sort of being ready to go plug and play.
然后只需随时准备好即插即用。
And this ensures that the developer or the user, so
这确保了开发者或用户，因此
he doesn't need to be concerned about anything beyond the necessary parts.
他不需要担心超出必要部分的任何事情。
And the essential bits of configuration and bootstrapping.
以及必要的配置和引导程序部分。
We've also gone ahead and developed some existing code for this.
我们还继续开发了一些现有的代码。
That works relatively simply, it connects to other machines in one-hop, Wi Fi or
它的工作原理相对简单，它可以一跳之達地连接到其他设备，无论是通过 Wi-Fi 还是
Ethernet range, and ensures that you get sort of the relevant components.
它确保你能够得到相关的部件，并覆盖以太网的范围。
So here, we have a sort of quick demo that I'm just gonna go ahead and
所以在这里，我们有一个快速的演示，我就直接去进行了
play for everyone.
为大家表演。
We have two Raspberry Pi's and one Mac.
我们有两个树莓派和一台Mac电脑。
The Mac NFT, which you can see on the right, was up and
右边的Mac NFT已经启动，而树莓派没有。
running the Pis were not.
树莓派还没有运行。
The three devices were sort of connected through Ethernet, and
这三个设备通过以太网连接起来了，而且
on Mac we have a server up and running.
在Mac上，我们已经有一个服务器正在运行。
That will generate a trust anchor certificate schema, for
这将生成一个信任锚证书架构，用于
devices, and listen to requests for distributing them.
设备，并监听分发这些请求。
And we'll see in the demo that the Raspberry Pi's, will
在演示中我们将看到，树莓派将会
start with the default identities, and then they will request the relevant bits.
从默认身份开始，然后它们将请求相关的数据位。
And it will get them and
它会获取它们并且
they will be installed in a sort of hard coded location.
它们将被安装在一种硬编码的位置。
Though in this demo the server is the one assigning the names and
尽管在这个演示中，服务器是负责分配名称的，
the identities, that's not actually necessary.
在这个演示中，虽然服务器是负责分配名称的，分配身份并不是必须的。
And the code itself does support the Raspberry Pis or
以及代码本身确实支持树莓派或
whoever else is running this to request a name and the server.
请求一个名称和服务器。
Can then discriminate whether or not it's going to be giving out that certificate.
然后可以判断是否会颁发该证书。
Or you could certainly use something like NDN cert,
或者你当然可以使用类似于NDN证书这样的东西，
which would do out of band methods and has already developed.
它会执行带外方法并且已经开发出来了。
>> John, you are almost out of time.
>> 约翰，你快没有时间了。
>> Yes, and from here you can see we're just going to, sort of print out
>> 是的，从这里你可以看到我们将要打印出来
the relevant certificates, which, take my word on it, they're in the proper place.
相关的证书，相信我，它们都放在了正确的地方。
So from there, just to briefly talk about future directions We want to further
所以从那里开始，仅仅简要地谈谈未来的方向，我们想要进一步
clarify and iron down the difference between IP and NDN configuration.
澄清并明确IP与NDN配置之间的差异。
We want to develop the automation tools for reachability.
我们想要开发用于实现可达性的自动化工具。
And on the topic of configuration, we also want to extend this to be flexible.
关于配置的话题，我们还想让它更加灵活。
So you can go through this configuration process multiple times to retrieve either
所以你可以多次进行这个配置过程，以检索不同的内容，比如
more identities or different certificates, so on and so forth.
因此，可以使用更多的身份标识或不同的证书等等。
So in conclusion, IP configuration is concerned solely with connectivity so
所以总的来说，IP配置仅仅关注于连通性，因此
the host can send and receive IP packets.
主机可以发送和接收IP数据包。
And the application itself has to configure security,
应用程序本身还必须配置安全性，
which we've seen comes with some vulnerabilities and some disadvantages.
它伴随着一些漏洞和缺点。
Whereas NDN entities take their name from the application and
然而，NDN实体的命名来自于应用程序，并且
then configure their security.
然后配置它们的安全性。
Which requires bootstrapping of both names and securities,
这需要对名称和安全措施进行引导设置，
which in turn requires authenticity.
这反过来又需要真实性。
And then once you're configured, you can do reachability in any number of ways.
然后一旦你配置好了，你就可以通过多种方式进行可达性测试。
And so that's how we see plug and
然后，这就是我们看到插件和
play proceeding in named data networking in the future.
在未来的命名数据网络中进行播放。
And that's about what I have.
这就是我所知道的全部内容。
So if anyone has any questions, I would welcome them.
所以如果有人有任何问题，我都欢迎提问。
>> Well, there is a few questions on the chat and
嗯，聊天里有一些问题，
I would recommend you do that because we're completely out of time.
我建议你这么做，因为我们完全没有时间了。
>> Sure, sorry about that.
>> 当然，对此我感到抱歉。
>> I think we should move.
>> 我认为我们应该搬家。
Yeah, check the chat and please answer to the questions on the chat.
好的，请查看聊天记录，并回答聊天中的问题。
So now we move to the second presentation.
那么现在我们来进行第二个演讲。
And the presentation is by Saurab Dulal
那么演讲将由Saurab Dulal来进行。
who is currently doing a PhD in computer
他目前正在孟菲斯大学攻读计算机科学博士学位。
science at the University of Memphis and
他目前正在孟菲斯大学攻读计算机科学，并且自2017年起参与NDN研究。
is involved in NDN research since 2017.
自2017年起参与NDN研究。
With areas of research in routing, IoT,
在路由、物联网等研究领域，
data synchronization, all of it in NDN, so Saurab, please.
在NDN中进行数据同步，所以Saurab，请。>> Thank you so much.
>> Thank you so much.
>> 非常感谢你。
Hello, everyone.
大家好。
So today I'm going to present a research and that is NDNSD.
所以今天我将要介绍的研究是NDNSD。
It is a service publishing and discovery in NDN.
它是NDN中的服务发布和发现。
So I'm Saurab Dulal and I'm from the University of Memphis.
所以我是Saurab Dulal，我来自孟菲斯大学。
So, service discovery is very important in modern applications,
因此，在现代应用程序中，服务发现非常重要，
whether it be IoT or mobile applications.
因此，在现代应用程序中，服务发现非常重要，无论是物联网还是移动应用程序。There are so many use cases of it like discovering printer,
There are so many use cases of it like discovering printer,
在现代应用程序中，服务发现的用例非常多，比如发现打印机，
service storage devices, and so on.
服务存储设备等。
So when we were doing this building management system project, we faced
所以当我们在进行这个建筑管理系统项目时，我们面临着
a several challenge because of the lack of service discovery mechanism in NDM,
多个挑战，因为在NDM中缺乏服务发现机制，
and we had to do a lot of this manual configuration.
我们不得不进行大量的手动配置。
And we started looking at some of the existing solution and
我们开始研究一些现有的解决方案，
we found out that either some of the solutions were centralized.
我们发现有些解决方案是集中式的。
And so all the solutions were limited to very specific environment.
因此所有的解决方案都局限于非常特定的环境中。
And in most of the solutions, we found out that the absence of higher level APIs.
在大多数解决方案中，我们发现缺少高级别的应用程序编程接口（API）。
So applications were forced to deal with a lower level network primitives.
因此，应用程序不得不处理较低级别的网络原语。
That's why our primary research goal is to design a general
因此，我们的主要研究目标是设计一个通用的
purpose distributed service discovery protocol for NDN.
因此，我们的主要研究目标是设计一个通用的，目的是为NDN设计一个分布式服务发现协议，并且可以支持各种类型的服务和。
And that can support various types of services and
应用场景。
cover a wide range of environment.
覆盖广泛的环境。
And we also want to develop a reusable library component and
我们还希望开发一个可重用的库组件以及
also provide higher level APIs.
同时提供更高层次的API。
So this will facilitate application developer to implement their own logic,
因此，这将便于应用开发人员实现他们自己的逻辑，
without having trouble to deal with those lower level network primitives.
因此，这将避免应用开发人员处理那些较低层次的网络原语所带来的麻烦。
But the obvious possible solution is to flooding, flood the network, and
但显而易见的可能解决方案是进行洪泛，淹没网络，
the consumer will flood the request.
消费者将会大量发出请求。
And whoever provides the service we'll serve the request.
无论是谁提供服务，我们都将响应请求。
But things will start getting complicated when this network size grows.
但是当这个网络的规模增长时，事情将开始变得复杂。
And obviously flooding will not scale.
显然，洪泛式方法是无法扩展的。
Other solution is to move the discovery to a rendezvous point or to a cloud.
另一种解决方案是将发现过程移至一个集合点或云端。
But with this solution, there are some problems.
但是这种解决方案存在一些问题。
We don't want a centralized solution because it can incur a single point
我们不想要一个中心化的解决方案，因为它可能导致单点
of failure.
故障的单点。
It can have an extra compute time, even for
它甚至可能会有额外的计算时间，即使对于
this kind of services that are very close to each other.
这种服务彼此非常接近。
They have to incur this extra round trip.
他们必须承担这个额外的往返。
And there can also be some external dependencies in some cases.
在某些情况下，也可能存在一些外部依赖。
So we don't want a centralized solution.
所以我们不希望有一个中心化的解决方案。
So we want something that is decentralized.
所以我们想要的是一种去中心化的东西。
So our solution is to group the services by the service type.
所以我们的解决方案是按照服务类型对服务进行分组。
For instance, printers, servers, or stories like that,
例如，打印机、服务器或者类似的故事，
depending on what type of service they are.
取决于它们是什么类型的服务。
And use a synchronizing protocol to synchronize the metadata of the services
并使用同步协议来同步服务的元数据。
are under common name prefix.
使用通用名称前缀。
For instance, printers will be under this name prefix and
例如，打印机将使用这个名称前缀，而
servers will be underneath.
服务器将位于下方。
>> Sir, sorry to interrupt, but your slides are not transitioning.
先生，很抱歉打扰一下，但您的幻灯片没有切换。
You're still on your title slide.
您还停留在标题幻灯片上。
>> Okay, so- >> Yes, now it's moving.
>> 好的，那么- >> 是的，现在它在动了。
>> Okay, so are we on the our solution slide right now.
>> 好的，那么我们现在是在我们的解决方案幻灯片上吗。
>> Yes.
>> 是的。
>> Okay, so these were the slide I missed.
>> 好的，所以这些是我错过的幻灯片。
Should I go?
我应该走吗？
Okay, I'll just go ahead from here.
好的，我会从这里开始。
So the solution is to group the services based on the service side,
所以解决方案是根据服务端来对服务进行分组，
that is printer and servers.
这是打印机和服务器。
As I said earlier, and use the synchronizing protocol to synchronize
正如我之前所说，使用同步协议进行同步。
the service under the common name prefix, that is printers will use this namespace,
服务将使用公共名称前缀，也就是打印机将使用这个命名空间，
and servers will use this namespace, and so on.
服务器也将使用这个命名空间等等。
And we provide a high level API with a well defined high level API.
我们提供了一个定义明确的高级API。
Currently we provide a service publisher API and service locator API.
目前我们提供了服务发布者API和服务定位器API。
Publisher API is used to serve the publish the service and
服务发布者API用于发布服务，以及
the locator API is used to locate the service.
定位器API用于定位服务。
So if you look at this flow diagram, then this is a publisher
所以如果你看这个流程图，这就是一个发布者。
application which receives an request from the user to publish a service and
应用程序接收来自用户的请求以发布服务，并且
underneath it will use a sync to publish the service.
它将使用同步来发布服务。
So if the service already exists in the network, let's say the printer,
如果服务已经在网络上存在，比如说打印机，
the service names printer already exists, then it will just publish under that name.
如果服务名称打印机已经存在，那么它将直接以该名称发布。
If the service doesn't exist, for instance, I want to create a group for
如果服务不存在，例如，我想创建一个群组用于
a gaming application.
一个游戏应用程序。
Then the NNEFI specify some service type then this will be created on the fly,
然后NNEFI会指定一些服务类型，这些服务将会即时创建。
and it will be advertised throughout the network.
它将会在整个网络中进行广播。
On the locator side, if some requests comes in like, for instance,
在定位器这一端，如果比如说有一些请求进来，
I want to look at all the printers.
我想查看所有的打印机。
Then the locator application will fetch all the names,
然后定位器应用程序将获取所有的名称，
the corresponding names and these names are basically application names.
对应的名称，这些名称基本上是应用程序的名称。
I'll talk about this names later on the later slide.
稍后我会在后面的幻灯片上讨论这些名称。
And it will fit these names and then face the individual service info and
我将会适配这些名称，然后对应个别的服务信息。
will provide the reply back to the user.
我将会回复用户。
For instance, printer one and this is the service info, and printer two and
例如，打印机一，这是服务信息，以及打印机二和
this is service and also for coarser servicing provided.
这是服务，也是提供的粗略服务。
So the rationale what is the what is the reason we are using a single sink for
所以逻辑是什么，我们使用单个水槽的原因是什么？
the service discovery.
服务发现。
So, sync provider pops up, which simplifies the discovery process.
因此，同步提供者出现了，这简化了发现过程。
Because if you see the discovery process then it basically is somebody trying to
因此，如果你看到了发现过程，那么它基本上是某人试图
publish some service and someone else trying to fetch the service.
发布某项服务并且其他人尝试获取该服务。
So it's a sort of kind of pub-sub model.
所以这是一种发布-订阅模型。
So we decided to use sync, and using sync is very flexible to implement
所以我们决定使用同步，使用同步来实现非常灵活。
the application semantic because several party can agree on a common sync group.
因为几个参与方可以就一个共同的同步组达成一致，所以这对应用语义来说是有益的。
And without caring about all those details,
而且不用关心所有那些细节，
they can agree on a common sync group and that will work perfectly fine.
他们可以就一个共同的同步组达成一致，这样会非常好用。
And there are also other benefits of using sync, but
还有使用同步的其他好处，但是
these are two important benefits.
这是两个重要的好处。
So talking about the design features,
所以谈到设计特点，
we offer a hierarchical namespace design, which has two types of prefix.
我们提供了一个分层的命名空间设计，它有两种类型的前缀。
One is a discovery prefix and another application prefix.
一个是发现前缀，另一个是应用前缀。
So discovery prefix is very flexible and this will
所以发现前缀非常灵活，这将会
be based on the what type of service the service provider is going to offer.
根据服务提供商将要提供的服务类型来决定。
For instance, here, you can see there is a route which can be organized and or
例如，在这里，你可以看到有一条可以组织的路线。
home or anything and there is a discovery under the new route.
家中或任何地方，新路线下有一个发现。
And these are the type of the services.
这些就是服务的类型。
For instance, image processing is one type of services,
例如，图像处理就是一种服务类型，
a lot of applications in these days were concerned about this kind of service.
现在许多应用程序都关注这类服务。
Similarly, there can be server printers or any other computers on surfaces.
同样，表面上也可以有服务器打印机或任何其他计算机。
And these services who actually offer the services can
同样，提供服务的这些服务可以
be grouped under this namespace and the application prefix or
可以归类到这个命名空间以及应用程序前缀或者
the name prefix that carries the service info.
可以归类到这个命名空间以及携带服务信息的应用程序前缀。
So, if you look at this design application data namespace design, then,
所以，如果你看这个设计应用程序数据的命名空间设计，那么，
there's a group which is pretty much same with the previous route.
这个组和之前的路线几乎是一样的。
And this is the actual service provider.
这就是实际的服务提供商。
So, the printer one is for service provider and the service-info.
所以，打印机这个是为了服务提供商和服务信息。
The printer one will have a bunch of service-info like what kind of
所以，打印机这个是为了服务提供商和服务信息，会有很多服务信息，比如它是什么样的printer it is and what kind of service it provides.
printer it is and what kind of service it provides.
它是什么样的打印机以及它提供哪些服务。
And similarly, more granular information can also be here, like for instance,
类似地，更详细的信息也可以在这里找到，例如，
the location of the printer itself, like library or some other things.
打印机的位置，比如图书馆或者其他地方。
So, in the sync level, these two namespace will be,
所以，在同步级别上，这两个命名空间将会是，
this prefix will be used like this.
这个前缀将会这样使用。
So, the printer, this is a service group and this also is a sync group.
所以，打印机，这是一个服务组，同时这也是一个同步组。
And this is a content that the sync group will carry, basically,
这是同步组将要处理的内容，基本上，
the sync will carry.
同步将会执行。
It will carry the all the name application prefix within the synchro and whenever,
同步中将携带所有名称应用前缀，无论何时，
whoever fetches this content, they can retrieve the individual service-info.
无论谁获取这些内容，他们都可以检索到各自的服务信息。
And in our case, which is a service locator.
在我们的情况下，它是一个服务定位器。
The all service design feature is service-info,
在我们的情况下，它是一个服务定位器，它基本上是一个服务细节。
which is basically a service detail.
它基本上是一个服务细节。
So, this will provide a great opportunity for,
所以，这将为……提供一个很好的机会。
to generalize the service discovery protocol.
因此，这将为推广服务发现协议提供一个很好的机会。
Because in service detail, based on what type of service you're offering,
因为在服务详情中，根据你提供的服务类型，
you can have as many as description as possible here.
您可以在这里尽可能地添加更多的描述。
So, for instance, for this specific type of service here, image processing,
所以，例如，对于这里的这种特定类型的服务，图像处理，
the description here, release here, and there's a lifetime.
所以，描述在这里，发布在这里，还有一个永久期限。
So, lifetime, basically, this is used, for
所以，基本上，这是用来……
instance, some type of service are very sensitive to the lifetime.
因此，某些类型的服务对于生命周期非常敏感。
Some, I offer this service only for 50 seconds and
因此，我只提供这项服务50秒钟，
it will expire after that second.
它将在那一秒后过期。
So, we use this lifetime along with the publish timestamp of the service to
因此，我们结合服务的发布时间戳和这个生命周期来
compute either the service is expired or is still active, and
计算服务是已过期还是仍然有效，并且
this information would be provided to the service locator.
这些信息将被提供给服务定位器。
And this will help to generalize the protocol for
这将有助于推广协议的通用性，以便
a wide range of applicantion because they can implement their own type of,
这将有助于推广协议的通用性，以便它们可以实施自己的类型的，
they can specify their own type of service detail.
他们可以指定自己的服务细节类型。
Along with this, the API,
可以通过API提供这些信息，
a law of measurement information can also be provided, is also provided via API.
这些测量信息的法则也可以通过API提供。
For instance, a round trip time to the service.
例如，到服务的往返时间。
This has the network level information you can provide to the service locator so
这包含了您可以提供给服务定位器的网络级别信息，以便
that it can do the QS or other other type of thing.
这样它就可以执行QS或其他类型的事务。
But with round trip time, one can look at the closest gateway or hub.
但是通过往返时间，人们可以查找最近的网关或中心。
And with service stability, if the service locator want to figure out the service
通过服务稳定性，如果服务定位器想要确定服务位置，
stability, then the periodic probing, the NDNSD library can do a periodic
稳定性，然后是周期性探测，NDNSD库可以执行周期性探测。
probing and then find out how to stable the services similarly retransmission
探测然后找出如何同样地稳定服务，以及如何进行重传。
count to the fetch service, and this information can be provided via the API.
计数到获取服务，这些信息可以通过API提供。
The other important aspects is accessibility.
其他重要方面是无障碍性。
So, someone who fetches the service info probably need to be
所以，获取服务信息的人可能需要被授权访问服务信息。
authorized to access the service-info.
授权访问服务信息。
So, how do you protect that?
那么，你是如何保护的呢？
How do you protect some sensitive information being displayed to
那么，你是如何保护一些敏感信息不被未经授权的观众看到的呢？
an unauthorized audience?
未经授权的观众？
So, we plan to use a name based access control.
所以，我们计划使用基于名称的访问控制。
Latin already presented.
拉丁文已经呈现。
Sometimes, I go about the NAC.
有时候，我会去NAC那边。
So, this basically, the service-info will, the content that is
所以，基本上，服务信息将会，内容即是
basically a service info will be encrypted using a CK, that is a content key.
所以，基本上，服务信息将会使用一个内容密钥，即是CK来加密。
And this content key will be decrypted, encrypted using a key,
而这个内容密钥将会被解密、使用一个密钥进行加密，
encryption key, which is obtained from the access manager.
加密密钥，这个是从访问管理器中获得的。
So, both of these content will be provided to,
因此，这两部分内容都将提供给，
will we passed onto the service locator.
将会传递给服务定位器。
After the service locator will get this content, it will face the KDK,
在服务定位器获取了这个内容之后，它将面临KDK，
which is key decryption key.
它是关键的解密密钥。
Decrypt this content key and then, finally,
解密这个内容密钥，然后，最终，
decrypt the content and get the content.
解密这个内容并获取内容。
So, this is based on the, sort of access policy,
那么，这是基于某种访问策略，
if the user is authorized to access this content or not.
如果用户被授权访问这些内容。
If he's authorized, it can access all the ways he can.
如果他被授权，他就可以访问所有的方式。
So, this is the use case and this is also our motivations where this,
所以，这就是用例，也是我们的动机所在，即在这里，
everything started.
一切都开始了。
So, we were doing this BMS project that I've said already.
所以，我们正在做这个我已经提过的建筑管理系统项目。
This is a simple building management system project where the parties involved
这是一个简单的建筑管理系统项目，其中涉及的各方包括
are sensor, repos, and a user.
参与方包括传感器、代码仓库和用户。
So, the basic flow is,
所以，基本的流程是，
sensor wants to discover the respective repo where it can insert the data to.
传感器想要发现它可以插入数据的相应仓库。
So, it will use NDNSD to discover the repos.
因此，它将使用NDNSD来发现这些仓库。
For instance, these repos will,
例如，这些仓库将会，
are willing to insert whatever the sensor will produce the data.
愿意插入任何传感器将会产生的数据。
So, it will discover the possible repos.
因此，它将会发现可能的仓库。
For instant, these three repos are here and it discovered the repos using an NDNSD
例如，这三个仓库就在这里，它通过NDNSD发现了这些仓库。
and it will use one of these repo to do the data transport.
它将使用其中一个仓库来进行数据传输。
Once the data is received by the repo, the data will be replicated among all these
一旦仓库接收到数据，这些数据将会在所有这些仓库之间复制。
repos using a sync protocol underneath, and then the data will be replicated.
使用同步协议的仓库下面，然后数据将会被复制。
Now, once the user wants to fetch some data, it will
现在，一旦用户想要获取一些数据，它将会
first discover all the prefixes that particular repo serves the data for.
首先发现那个特定仓库为哪些前缀服务提供数据。
So, this is an interesting application.
所以，这是一个有趣的应用程序。
>> I gave you a few more minutes, but I hope you're at the end.
我给了你多几分钟，但我希望你已经快要完成了。
>> Yeah, I'm [INAUDIBLE].
是的，我[不可辨识]。
And he will discover all the prefixes and
他将会发现所有的前缀和
then it will fetch the corresponding data from the repo.
然后它将从仓库中获取相应的数据。
So, this is a entire use case.
所以，这是一个完整的用例。
With our discovery protocol here,
使用我们这里的发现协议，
it will be really painful to do all this configuration manually.
手动进行所有这些配置将会非常痛苦。
So, we did some of the preliminary evaluation.
所以，我们进行了一些初步评估。
We set up the testbed in University of Memphis using Raspberry Pi's, and
我们在孟菲斯大学使用树莓派搭建了测试平台，并且
we did some experiments with distance and and also for the condition.
我们进行了一些关于距离和条件的实验。
These are the distribution of the Raspberry Pi across the Dunn Hall,
这些是树莓派在邓恩大厅的分布情况，
the University of Memphis.
孟菲斯大学。
And we also did some wired and wireless simulations.
我们还进行了有线和无线的模拟测试。
We have our implementation on top of PSync and
我们的实现是基于PSync之上的，
Chronosync which are actively maintained sync protocol right now, and
我们目前积极维护的同步协议就是Chronosync，而且
the NDNSDs can adopt to both of these protocol.
NDNSDs能够适配这两种协议。
So, one of the evaluation that I would like to share here is from the mini-NDN,.
因此，我想在这里分享的一个评估来自mini-NDN。
This is a emulation experiment.
这是一个仿真实验。
So, data, there are multi hop involved, this is a multi hop policy.
因此，数据中涉及了多跳传输，这是一种多跳传输策略。
Service-info upgrade frequency is 900 milliseconds per 200 milliseconds jitter,
服务信息升级频率为每900毫秒，加上200毫秒的抖动。
which is how often the service-info is updated.
这就是服务信息更新的频率。
And total number of upgrade is 300 per producer.
每个生产者的升级总数是300次。
The protocol users, PSync and Link-delay was 10 millisecond.
协议用户，PSync和Link-delay的延迟是10毫秒。
So, you see, if this, you see at this delays, then these are lower,
所以，你看，如果这样，你看这些延迟，那么这些是较低的，
lesser than the actual delay that should be there.
比实际应有的延迟要少。
For instance, the round trip time for this one,
例如，这个的往返时间，
from the point where the publisher publishes the service and
从发布者发布服务的那一刻起，
the sync propagate this information to the consumer, which is 10 millisecond around,
从发布者发布服务的那一刻起，同步将这些信息传播到消费者大约需要10毫秒，
and then fetching the service-info is another 20 millisecond, so
所以，再获取服务信息又需要大约20毫秒，
which is about 30 millisecond, but it comes down to 25 milliseconds, and
大约是30毫秒，但它降到了25毫秒，以及
it happens for all the hops here.
它发生在这里的所有跳数上。
So, this is very, this is due to the in-network caching of NDN also and
所以，这很大程度上是由于NDN中的网络内缓存，同时也是由于同步多播。
also due to the sync multicast.
也是由于同步多播。
So, this is reducing the overall delay.
因此，这减少了整体的延迟。
So, this is one of the benefit of using multicasting, multicast and
因此，这是使用多播的好处之一，多播并且
multicasting of NDN.
多播NDN。
So, in conclusion, we develop a general-purpose,
总的来说，我们正在开发一个通用的，
we're developing a general-purpose, a distributed service publishing and
我们正在开发一个通用的、分布式的服务发布和发现机制，用于NDN。
discovery mechanism for NDN.
我们为NDN开发了一种发现机制。
We defined well-defined pub-sub API for discovery and reusable library components
我们为发现机制定义了明确的发布-订阅API和可复用的库组件。
are there and we'll share some of the preliminary evaluation and use-case.
我们将分享一些初步的评估和用例。
Some of the existing difficulties that we're facing is to set up a real-world
我们面临的一些现有困难是建立一个真实世界的
testbed and also do experiment.
我们面临的一些现有困难是建立一个真实世界的测试床并进行实验。One of the problem that we faced was due to lack of multicast suppression in NFD.
One of the problem that we faced was due to lack of multicast suppression in NFD.
我们面临的一个问题是由于NFD中缺乏多播抑制功能。
We observe enormous amount of unsolicited data and interest.
我们观察到大量的非请求数据和兴趣。
And this was causing a huge condition in the network.
这导致了网络中的一个巨大问题。
So, we are not, I was practically when doing experiment wasn't able to go
所以，我们不能，实际上在做实验时我几乎无法进行
beyond 10 to 12 nodes in a MESS setup, in one hop MESS setup.
在一个跳的MESS设置中，超出10到12个节点。
So, the future work was, is to perform some scaling experiment in mini-NDN.
因此，未来的工作是在mini-NDN中进行一些扩展实验。
And also, do some real world multi-hop wireless experiments and
还有，进行一些真实世界的多跳无线实验和
also to implement the use case that I have seen earlier
还要实现我之前看到的用例
to completely implement the use case that I've seen earlier and do more evaluation.
还要完全实现我之前看到的用例，并进行更多的评估。
Thank you.
谢谢。
>> Thank you very much.
>> 非常感谢。
There's a lot of activity on the chats that I suppose to be able to look at.
在我应该能查看的聊天中有很多活动。
And so, for the sake of timing, because it's really close to
为了掌握时间，因为真的很接近
when we should stop and we still have a presentation,
为了掌握时间，因为真的很接近，当我们应该停下来而我们还有一个演讲时，I would suggest that we take the questions to the chat.
I would suggest that we take the questions to the chat.
我建议我们把问题带到聊天中去。
>> Okay, sure.
>> 好的，当然可以。
>> And so, thank you very much.
>> 非常感谢您。
So, the last but not the least, so it's the last and the last of the last.
所以，这是最后一个，而且是最最后一个。
We have a presentation from Susmit Shannigrahi
我们有来自Susmit Shannigrahi的演讲。
from Tennessee Tech where he is an assistant professor.
他是田纳西科技大学的助理教授。
We're looking and doing research in Networking for Big Science,
我们正在大科学领域的网络方面进行研究，
obviously future Internet Architecture and also 5G Mobile Networks.
我们显然还在研究未来的互联网架构以及5G移动网络。
And he's going to share the presentation with Zhaoning Kong,
他将与孔兆宁一起分享这个演讲，
who is a PhD student at Purdue.
他是普渡大学的一名博士研究生。
And he used to be at UCLA for his master's and
他曾在加州大学洛杉矶分校攻读硕士学位，并且显然也对网络系统和分布式系统感兴趣。
is also interested obviously in Network System and Distribution System.
并且显然也对网络系统和分布式系统感兴趣。
And they will talk about an NDN-Repo for genomics datasets,
他们还将讨论用于基因组数据集的NDN-Repo，
which is the progress and future direction.
它是进展和未来的方向。
And I think a lot of people, it's interesting that we close with
我认为很有趣，我们最后讨论的是
this because I think we started with a presentation on NDN for large datasets.
我们之所以讨论这个，是因为我认为我们最初是从大数据集的NDN演示开始的。
So we're now closing the loop, so Susmit and
所以我们现在正在闭环，所以Susmit和
Zhaoning, please start your presentation.
赵宁，请开始你的演讲。
>> Okay, great, thank you for the introduction.
>> 好的，太好了，感谢你的介绍。
And as you said, we are closing the loop we opened with the genomics doc and
正如你所说，我们正在结束我们在基因组学文档中开始的循环，
now we're closing the cycle.
现在我们正在结束这个循环。
The motivation for this talk, so the Repo is a generic storage,
这次演讲的动机在于，Repo是一种通用存储，
it's not necessarily only for the genomics community.
它不一定只是为了基因组学社区。
But we are taking the genomics example, to drive the development for the repo.
但我们正在以基因组学为例，推动仓库的发展。
For those who were in the NDN community for a long time,
对于那些长期在NDN社区的人来说，
you might remember NDN-repo.
你可能还记得NDN-repo。
And it was again the same thing, it's a persistent repo that stores packet.
它又是同样的东西，它是一个持久性的仓库，用来存储数据包。
We took the genomics use case, and we found a few differences
我们研究了基因组学的用例，并发现了一些差异。
that we need to incorporate in the repo's design.
我们需要在代码仓库的设计中加入这些内容。
And we are going to go over those, give a little bit of experimental results.
我们将会审查这些内容，并提供一些实验结果。
But more importantly, it's still in the design and implementation phase, so
但更重要的是，它仍然处于设计和实施阶段，所以
if you have any feedback, that would be really appreciated.
如果您有任何反馈，我们将非常感激。
[COUGH] Okay, so as we saw in the first session that large science
[咳嗽] 好的，正如我们在第一场会议中看到的那样，大型科学数据集确实可以从NDN的基于名称的特性中受益。
datasets can really benefit from NDN's name-based,
数据集确实可以从NDN的基于名称的特性中受益。
and location transparent networking.
和位置透明的网络。
The one critical aspect of that is to have storage.
这其中一个关键方面是要有存储设备。
What are the properties that we need for scientific datasets?
我们需要科学数据集具备哪些属性？
They have to support very large data sets,
它们必须支持非常大的数据集，
anywhere from terabytes to petabytes.
它们必须支持从太字节到拍字节不等的非常大的数据集。
We have tested the new Python-Repo with over 1 terabytes of data.
我们已经用超过1太字节的数据测试了新的Python-Repo。
But again in Graham Scheme of Things,
但在Graham的整体计划中，
that's not too large, so we have a long way to go.
这并不算太大，因此我们还有很长的路要走。
It should provide the persistent storage at a file level.
它应该提供文件级别的持久存储。
So, even though NDN chunks files into packets,
所以，即使NDN将文件分割成数据包，
we are saying that because all these
我们是这么说的，因为所有这些
communities their unit of operation is file.
社区的运作单位是文件。
So it makes sense instead of just having all the packets at one place,
所以这样做是有道理的，与其把所有数据包放在一个地方，
we should have things stored at a file level granularity.
我们应该以文件级粒度来存储数据。
It should provide transparent data access to
它应该提供透明的数据访问权限给
the requesters who know where the data is located.
请求者应当了解数据所在的位置。
And then it has also be replicated for availability and
以及为了可用性而进行了复制
geographically distributed users.
地理分布的用户。
So all these communities most of them are pretty international.
所以这些社区中的大多数都是相当国际化的。
So they even nationally distributed, so we cannot have only one repo at one place and
因此，它们甚至是全国性分布的，所以我们不能只在一个地方有一个仓库，
tell everyone to go to that, that's not going to scale.
告诉每个人去那里，那是不可扩展的。
So for the genomics use case,
所以对于基因组学的用例来说，
we wanted the publishers to publish data sets into the repo.
我们希望出版商能将数据集发布到仓库中。
And they could use their own community defined names.
他们可以使用自己社区定义的名称。
So if the same repo is storing physics and
因此，如果同一个仓库存储的是物理学和基因组数据集，它应该同时支持社区定义的命名方案。
Instead of saying that this is a repo that I'm running,
相反，不要说这是我在管理的一个仓库，
everything that you publish from here must have the same prefix.
您从这里发布的所有内容都必须有相同的前缀。
The second point is data is automatically replicated.
第二点是数据会自动复制。
So the degree of replication is defined by use cases.
因此，复制的程度是由用例来定义的。
The genomics community might have three degree of replications,
基因组学社区可能有三个复制程度，
others might have more.
其他人可能会有更多。
It should automatically maintain the degree of replication when
它应该能够自动维持复制的程度当
failure happens.
发生故障。
So if a replica goes down, it needs to replicate
所以如果一个副本发生故障，它需要复制
that failed content to another instance of repo.
所以如果一个副本发生故障，它需要复制那些失败的内容到另一个仓库实例中。
We're not going to go into the details of that, but that's how it should work.
我们不打算深入了解细节，但理论上应该是这样运作的。
Now, the other thing to know that the repo is a persistent storage.
现在，需要知道的另一件事是，这个仓库是一个持久存储。
But there is opportunity for creating another layer, on top of that,
但在其基础之上，还有机会创建另外一层，
that supports different use cases.
这支持不同的使用场景。
For example, genomics, we have data in the repo, but how do we figure out the names?
例如，在基因组学中，我们在仓库中有数据，但我们如何确定这些名字呢？
So we can have sort of a separate name catalog or
因此我们可以有一种独立的名字目录或者
database, where the scientists can go and look things up.
数据库，科学家们可以去查找信息。
If we have another example might be replication.
如果我们有另一个例子，可能是复制。
So you might have some sort of logic that says,
如果我们有某种逻辑，那么可能会说，
these are the top 10% of the datasets that are being used by the scientist.
这些是科学家们正在使用的数据集中最顶尖的10%。
So from Alex's talk,
所以从亚历克斯的演讲来看，
you might remember that there's 42 petabytes of genomics data.
你可能还记得有42佩他字节的基因组数据。
So obviously, all of that cannot be replicated multiple times.
显然，所有这些都不能被多次复制。
So you might create a thin layer on top of the repo that says,
因此，你可能会在仓库上方创建一个轻量级的层，这个层的作用是说，
this is the really popular data set and can benefit from NDN.
这是一个非常受欢迎的数据集，可以从NDN中受益。
So we are going to only replicate those datasets into the repo.
所以我们只会将那些数据集复制到仓库中。
So that's the high level view, I'm going to hand it over to Zhaoning for
所以这就是一个高层次的视角，接下来我将把它交给兆宁来负责。
the actual implementation and the details.
实际的执行和细节。
>> Hi, everyone, can you hear me?
>> 大家好，你们能听见我说话吗？
>> Yes.
>> 是的。
>> Hi, can you hear me?
>> 嗨，你能听见我吗？
>> Yes, I can hear you.
>> 是的，我能听见你。
>> Okay, hi, everyone, my name is Zhaoning and
>> 好的，大家好，我的名字是兆宁，
I'm gonna finish the rest of this talk.
我将完成这次谈话的剩余部分。
So first I'd like to start with overview of the NDN-Repo.
首先，我想从NDN-Repo的概述开始讲起。
So, on the slide, you can see there's two graphs.
所以，在幻灯片上，你可以看到有两个图表。
The graph on the left is showing how application inserts file into the repo.
左边的图表展示了应用程序如何将文件插入到仓库中。
And on the right, you can see how the application retrieves data from the repo.
右边的图表展示了应用程序如何从仓库中检索数据。
So, basically this is a reactive process.
所以，基本上这是一个反应式的过程。
The repo just sits there and waits for
仓库只是坐在那里等待着
the application to send a request as for insertion or data retrieval.
应用程序用于发送请求，以进行插入或数据检索。
And that's an assessment, next slide, please?
这是一个评估，下一张幻灯片，请？
So why do we want to do replication on NDN repos?
那么，我们为什么要在NDN仓库上进行数据复制呢？
So first by deploying a set of distributed repo nodes,
因此，首先通过部署一组分布式仓库节点，
waiting through the availability and performance of the entire system.
等待通过整个系统的可用性和性能。
Because the request doesn't have to go to one place,
因为请求不必只发送到一个地方，
it can go to many different places.
它可以发送到许多不同的地方。
And to this end, we're thinking of using any test, so basically
为此，我们考虑使用任何测试，基本上是这样。
All the repos can announce the same routing announcement and
所有的仓库都可以发布相同的路由公告，而且
an interest will be forwarded to the nearest repo.
一个兴趣将被转发到最近的仓库。
And the other thing is by replicating data files on multiple repo nodes,
通过在多个仓库节点上复制数据文件，
we avoid the single point of failure.
我们避免了单点故障。
And to make this work we are thinking of using consistent hashing
为了实现这一点，我们考虑使用一致性哈希。
to decide which file to be replicated on which node.
为了决定哪个文件应该被复制到哪个节点上。
And I will talk about how that is done in the next few slides.
接下来的几张幻灯片里，我将会讲解这是如何做到的。
Next slide please.
下一张幻灯片，请。
So, the high level idea of consistent hashing is that
所以，一致性哈希的高层次概念是
we have both repo node and files onto the same hash ring.
我们将存储库节点和文件都放置在同一个哈希环上。
So as you can see on the graph on the right,
所以正如你在右边的图表上看到的，
we have multiple repo nodes, A, B, C, D, and so on.
我们有多个仓库节点，比如A、B、C、D等等。
And we hash these nodes onto a hash ring.
我们将这些节点哈希到一个哈希环上。
In the meantime, we also hash files or data onto this ring.
与此同时，我们也将文件或数据哈希到这个环上。
So for example, let's say there's a file called filename, and
所以举个例子，假设有一个叫做filename的文件，
we use hash function H1 and hash that to a place between node B and C.
我们使用哈希函数H1并将其哈希到节点B和C之间的某个位置。
And we use a convention saying that this file would be replicated,
我们采用一个约定，即这个文件将会被复制，
will be stored by the closest node smaller than it, in this case it is node B.
将会被存储在比它小的最近的节点，这种情况下是节点B。
Right, so and to step up the level,
好的，所以为了提高水平，
we can also use multiple hash functions so
我们还可以使用多个哈希函数，以便
that the same file can be replicated on multiple nodes.
以便同一个文件可以在多个节点上复制。
Next slide please.
下一张幻灯片，请。
So to make consistent hashing work,
为了使一致性哈希工作正常运行，
we need to have a Membership Management Protocol.
为了使一致性哈希工作正常运行，我们需要有一个成员管理协议。
Which enables each repo node to have a global view of a list of all
该协议使得每个仓库节点都能够全局查看所有节点的列表。
other members, so that each of them can construct such a ring.
以便它们每个人都能够构建这样的环。
And also each node have to quickly learn that a new node has joined or
并且每个节点还需要迅速了解到一个新节点已经加入或者
an existing node has failed.
一个现有的节点已经出现故障。
So to make this work we're currently thinking of
所以为了让这个工作正常运行，我们目前正在考虑
having each node periodically ping is next neighbor.
因此，每个节点会定期对它的下一个邻居发送ping信号。
And this ping message will contain a membership list with timestamp.
这个ping消息将包含一个带有时间戳的成员列表。
So that this membership list will be circulated around the ring and
这样这个成员列表将会在环中传递。
gets everyone updated about what's the list of current members.
这样可以让每个人都知道当前成员列表的情况。
And also for fast failure discovery, we can broadcast the failure messages,
为了快速发现故障，我们可以广播故障消息，
so it so that it gets propagated to everyone immediately.
以便它能立即传播给每个人。
And for new nodes to join we can set a predefined namespace, for
为了让新节点加入，我们可以设置一个预定义的命名空间，用于
example, repo_group/join.
为了让新节点加入，我们可以设置一个预定义的命名空间，用于例子中的repo_group/join。每当有新节点加入时，它就可以向这个前缀发送一个兴趣。
And whenever a new node comes, it can send an interest to this prefix.
每当有新节点加入时，它就可以向这个前缀发送一个兴趣。
And this interest will be routed in anycast fashion to one of the nodes and
这个兴趣将以任播的方式路由到其中一个节点，
that node will include this new node into the array.
该节点将把这个新节点加入到数组中。
Yeah, this is how we handle membership management.
是的，这就是我们处理会员管理的方式。
And in the next slide, I will talk about how we insert and
在下一张幻灯片中，我将讨论我们如何插入和
retrieve data from this replicated repo.
从这个复制的仓库中检索数据。
Next slide please.
下一张幻灯片，请。
So to insert data into the repo, we're thinking of using anycast.
因此，为了将数据插入仓库，我们考虑使用任播技术。
Physically, the app sends insert request, and
物理上，应用程序发送插入请求，
this request will be routed in anycast style to the nearest neighbor.
这个请求将以任播方式路由至最近的邻居节点。
Let's say for example, in the graph on the right,
例如，在右边的图中，
let's say that this interest gets routed to H.
假设这个请求被路由到了H。
And then node H will look at this hash ring and decide that,
然后节点H会查看这个哈希环，并决定，
okay, this file is gonna be replicated on nodes B, D, and F.
好的，这个文件将会在节点B、D和F上进行复制。
And then it will send requests through these three nodes and
然后它会通过这三个节点发送请求。
ask them to replicate this file.
让他们复制这个文件。
And retrieving data from the repo is a similar process.
从仓库中检索数据是一个类似的过程。
Basically the application was in the interest to one of the nodes, but
基本上，应用程序对其中一个节点感兴趣，但是
this node may not necessarily hold the data.
这个节点可能并不一定持有数据。
So it will look at the hash ring, and decide, and
所以它会查看哈希环，然后做出决定，以及
find out which node holds this data.
确定哪个节点持有这个数据。
And then retrieve the file from that node and send it back to the application.
然后从那个节点检索文件，并将其发送回应用程序。
Next slide please.
下一张幻灯片，请。
So the last slide talks about how we- >> Am sorry to interrupt but
很抱歉打断一下，但是
you only have few minutes left.
您只剩下几分钟了。
>> Right, this is my last slide.
>> 好的，这是我的最后一张幻灯片。
So there are two cases here, have one existing nodes fail.
所以这里有两种情况，有一个现有的节点失败了。
For this case we can use a convention saying that the next clockwise node is
在这种情况下，我们可以采用一个约定，即下一个顺时针方向的节点是
responsible for failure recovery.
负责故障恢复。
For example, let's say that node B failed and
例如，假设节点B发生了故障并且
node D, in this case would be responsible for
节点D在这种情况下将负责
doing failure recovery for the files, it shares with B.
负责对它与B共享的文件进行故障恢复。
And then it looks at the hash ring and figured out A will be responsible for
然后它查看哈希环并确定A将负责对它与B共享的文件进行故障恢复。
these files after B failed, and initiate the failure recovery process.
它会在B出故障后处理这些文件，并启动故障恢复过程。
And when you know joins, that's also pretty simple.
当你了解了连接（joins）的时候，这也相当简单。
Basically, the next clockwise node will figure
基本上，下一个顺时针方向的节点将会计算出哪些文件将被移动到新节点。
out which files will be moved to the new node.
将会计算出哪些文件将被移动到新节点。
Next slide please.
下一张幻灯片，请。
So in the end, I would like to talk about some of the future works.
所以最后，我想谈谈一些未来的工作。
So first, I think is one step would be to enhance the repo with file semantics.
所以首先，我认为应该采取的一步是增强仓库的文件语义。
Because repo initially was designed so that it holds individual data packets.
因为最初仓库的设计是用来存放单独的数据包的。
However, during our actual deployment, we found that most application,
然而，在我们实际部署过程中，我们发现大多数应用程序，
insert and retrieve individual files from the repo.
将单个文件插入和从仓库中检索出来。
And by using file semantics, some things can be designed in a simpler way.
通过使用文件语义，一些事情可以设计得更简单。
For example, the replication process that I just talked about.
例如，我刚才谈到的复制过程。
And also I think it's important to update the repo protocol spec and
还有我认为更新仓库协议规范也很重要，并且
implement the repo replication process.
实现仓库复制过程。
The algorithm I just talked about.
我刚才谈到的算法。
And we're also thinking about publishing a tech report on the python repo and
我们还在考虑在Python仓库上发布一份技术报告，以及
the implementation.
实施情况。
Right, that's all thanks.
好的，就这些，谢谢。
>> Thank you very much.
>> 非常感谢。
Again, we have some discussions on the chat
我们在聊天中又有了一些讨论。
that I suggest that you have a look at.
我建议你看一看。
There's a few questions and a few comments and
有几个问题和一些评论。
it's exactly 5 PM and we were supposed to end at 5 PM.
现在正好是下午5点，我们原定的结束时间是下午5点。
So I will thank everyone to have lasted so
所以我要感谢大家坚持到现在。
long, thank you to all the presenters.
长时间以来，感谢所有的演讲者。
And I will hand it over to Lofty for, I guess the conclusion.
我将把最后的部分交给Lofty来完成，我猜这就是结论了。
Thank you very much, everyone.
非常感谢大家。
>> Okay, thanks Marie Josie, I guess we reached the end of NDN Count 2020.
好的，谢谢你，Marie Josie，我想我们已经到了NDN Count 2020的尾声了。
Many thanks again to all the session chairs,
再次感谢所有的会议主席，
the panel chairs, panelists and all the presenters.
会议小组主席、小组成员以及所有的报告者。
Just a couple of quick announcements one is, next week you should receive an email
只有几个简短的通知，一个是，下周您应该会收到一封电子邮件
from the NIST conference staff asking you for feedback on how this event went.
来自NIST会议工作人员的请求，希望您就此次活动的情况提供反馈。
This is first time we're doing NDN Community remotely, so
这是我们第一次远程举办NDN社区活动，所以
I'm sure we can do better next time.
我相信我们下次能做得更好。
And the second thing is that some of the attendees are asking whether we will
以及第二件事是，有些与会者在问我们是否会
make the slides available.
制作幻灯片供大家使用。
So I will send an email to all the presenters to get their
我将给所有的演讲者发一封邮件，以获得他们的许可，将幻灯片发布到网上。
permission to post the slides online.
获得授权将幻灯片发布到网上。
With that, thanks again everyone, and see you next time, I guess.
再次感谢大家，下次见了。
Bye bye, everyone.
再见，大家。
>> Thank you.
谢谢。
>> Thank you very much and Lofty by the way,
>> 非常感谢，顺便说一下，Lofty，
even if it was your first time it worked went really well.
即使这是你第一次尝试，但进行得非常顺利。
Congratulations to you and your team.
恭喜你和你的团队。
>> Thanks, we'll see you guys face here right here.
>> 谢谢，我们会在这里见面的。
>> Okay, thanks NIST for hosting this meeting, I think it's a great meeting.
>> 好的，感谢NIST主办这次会议，我认为这是一次非常棒的会议。
Thank you.
谢谢。